<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Latest &amp; Breaking News on Fox News</title>
        <link>https://www.foxnews.com/</link>
        <description>Discover the latest breaking news feed with Fox. Find out what the latest news is and read about the latest news happening today.</description>
        <copyright>Copyright 2024 FOX News Network</copyright>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:18:58 -0500</pubDate>
        
            <image>
                <url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</url>
                <title>Latest &amp; Breaking News on Fox News</title>
                <link>https://www.foxnews.com/</link>
            </image>
        
        <atom:link rel="self" href="https://moxie.foxnews.com/google-publisher/latest.xml?format=xml" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <atom:link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"/>

        

        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/law-enforcement-say-increase-us-highway-shootings-causing-more-problems-nationwide</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/law-enforcement-say-increase-us-highway-shootings-causing-more-problems-nationwide</guid>
                    <title>Law enforcement say an increase in US highway shootings is causing more problems nationwide</title>
                    
                    <description>Highway shootings are up across the country and police say there&amp;apos;s no clear solution. Law enforcement departments in at least six states reported more highway shootings since 2023.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The number of shootings on U.S. interstates is up across the country and a big reason for this is aggressive driving. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with more attention coming to this issue, it isn’t an easy fix according to the police.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;You have the recipe for some real, real challenges,&quot; said Chris Loftis with Washington State Patrol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington State Patrol is seeing more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/man-arrested-florida-road-rage-incident-started-tossed-cup-coffee-deputies&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;shootings on highways &lt;/a&gt;- and they’re hard to prevent.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/chicago-expressway-shootings-surge&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CHICAGO EXPRESSWAY SHOOTINGS CONTINUE TO SURGE DESPITE $12.5M GRANT, FEDERAL INTERVENTION&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Highways are dangerous enough without anything like this,&quot; Loftis said. &quot;It makes it tougher to patrol and respond. And then it makes it tougher to investigate.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Law enforcement attribute many of these &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/hero-texas-teen-drove-friends-safety-being-shot-heart-during-road-rage-incident&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;shootings to aggressive driving&lt;/a&gt; and the reaction from surrounding drivers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;When you have situations where peoples’ behavior is changing about how they’re operating their vehicles,&quot; Loftis said. &quot;And then peoples’ behavior changing in how they respond to aggressiveness. You overlay that with more people, more cars.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/california-motorists-caught-crosshairs-alarming-trend-freeway-gang-shootouts&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CALIFORNIA MOTORISTS CAUGHT IN CROSSHAIRS AMID ALARMING TREND OF FREEWAY GANG SHOOTINGS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last year, areas in Washington State, California, Wisconsin, Indiana, Pennsylvania and Florida have reported an increase in highway shootings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The numbers are just too high,&quot; said David Reich with the National Road Safety Foundation.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best advice for drivers is to try to drive carefully and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/colorado-road-rage-shooter-convicted-first-degree-murder&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;avoid aggressive drivers&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/california-freeway-shooting-leaves-1-person-dead-another-injured&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CALIFORNIA FREEWAY SHOOTINGS LEAVE 1 PERSON DEAD, ANOTHER INJURED&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Any time, if someone is driving aggressively, just try to stay away from them,&quot; Reich said. &quot;It’s human nature to want to curse the guy out or do something to retaliate. But it’s not worth it.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Washington State Patrol is fighting back with more officers on the road.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We’ve definitely put in more emphasis patrols and focused patrol units in certain parts,&quot; Loftis said. &quot;Especially since we’re seeing so much.&quot;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shortage of police officers has also made it tougher to crack down on these shootings.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/HIGHWAY-SHOOTINGS-1.png?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/png" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">613b84f9-be76-5cdf-8d60-0949bc1b439a</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/auto/news</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/west/washington</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime/police-and-law-enforcement</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/topic/fox-news-multimedia-reporters</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:18:58 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/bill-maher-urges-biden-lean-into-age</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/media/bill-maher-urges-biden-lean-into-age</guid>
                    <title>Bill Maher urges Biden to &apos;lean into&apos; his age, stop saying he&apos;s still sharp: &apos;Let his old fart flag fly!&apos;</title>
                    
                    <description>Liberal comedian Bill Maher urged President Biden to &amp;quot;lean into&amp;quot; his age and to stop pretending he&amp;apos;s still sharp as he heads into the presidential election.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&quot;Real Time&quot; host &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/bill-maher-cheers-dem-ny-special-election-successfully-flipped-immigration-issue-ran-right&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bill Maher&lt;/a&gt; closed his show Friday night by urging President Biden to &quot;lean into&quot; his age and &quot;let his old fart flag fly.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;If Democrats want to win the next presidential election, they need to find a way to make the Biden age issue work for them. Because you know what&apos;s really getting old about Joe Biden? Complaining about his age,&quot; Maher began his monologue about the 81-year-old president. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Instead of trying to refute all the ‘too old to be president’ slams, Joe must embrace them. Stop with the &apos;I&apos;m sharper than ever.&apos; Nobody&apos;s buying that. Don&apos;t try to deny the age thing, lean into it. Lean in, lean in like you&apos;re eating soup,&quot; Maher quipped. &quot;And just admit it! Say ‘Yes, I’m bad with names and I walk like a toddler with full diaper, but I believe in democracy.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/bill-maher-says-biden-switched-out-dnc-convention&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BILL MAHER SAYS BIDEN CAN BE SWITCHED OUT AT THE DNC CONVENTION: HE SOLD HIMSELF AS A ‘ONE TERM’ PRESIDENT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The HBO host said Democratic candidates have become &quot;defensive&quot; on who they really are, citing John Kerry&apos;s duck hunting and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/politics/the-clintons&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Hillary Clinton&lt;/a&gt; carrying hot sauce in her purse during their presidential bids, insisting &quot;Americans hate that s---.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Be yourself! And Joe, yourself is old,&quot; Maher told Biden before suggesting he &quot;take a page&quot; from the playbook of his &quot;old pal&quot; John McCain, who embraced his age during the 2008 presidential election. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/bill-maher-warned-dems-bidens-electability-long-before-explosive-special-counsel-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BILL MAHER WARNED DEMS ABOUT BIDEN&apos;S ELECTABLITY LONG BEFORE THE EXPLOSIVE SPECIAL COUNSEL REPORT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;No one cares if you can ride a bike and trying to do stuff like that is only setting yourself up for failure,&quot; Maher said while showing a photo of Biden when he fell off his bike. &quot;You recently joined TikTok to win over the kids, get off that s--- right now! It&apos;s inauthentic and it won&apos;t work! You&apos;re not following the demographics. In 2020, a record number of eligible voters under 24 came out – as gay! But came out to vote? Not so much. Less than half. But almost 72% of people over 65 voted. Those are your people, Joe. That ‘Matlock’ crowd. Reach out to them… Take all your ads of Twitter and put them on CBS. Tell America I feel your joint pain.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;When the president delivers the State of the Union, I say he should old fart flag fly,&quot; Maher added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maher went on to demonstrate how Biden&apos;s State of the Union address &quot;should&quot; look like, which included using a walker and unabashedly making gaffe after gaffe. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/bill-maher-rips-america-bashing-celebs-vowed-flee-country-under-trump-still-here&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BILL MAHER RIPS AMERICA-BASHING LIBERAL CELEBS WHO VOWED TO FLEE COUNTRY UNDER TRUMP: THEY’RE &apos;STILL HERE&apos;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Maher has long defended Biden against his &quot;agist&quot; critics, he has also repeatedly called him &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/bill-maher-promotes-ruth-bader-biden-merch-amid-push-bench-biden-doesnt-know-quit&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ruth Bader Biden&lt;/a&gt;,&quot; comparing him to the late Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, who famously chose not to step down under President Obama and allowed President Trump to appoint her replacement following her passing in 2020. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He most recently invoked the Ginbsurg comparison following the release of Special Counsel Robert Hur&apos;s report, which put a spotlight on Biden&apos;s mental acuity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I said he was going to be the Ruth Bader Ginsburg of presidential politics… He stayed too long at the fair,&quot; Maher said last month. &quot;Bubbling up this week… he won&apos;t do the Super Bowl interview, which is not a hard one, mixing up all the world leaders and then this report that came out.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biden&apos;s age and mental acuity continues to be a major issue for him going into the presidential election as the vast majority of Americans, including Democrats, believe he&apos;s too old to seek a second term.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/MaherBiden2.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">8e3ba4af-6eca-5a42-a6dd-1b46825dcb4b</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/entertainment/politics-on-late-night</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/joe-biden</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/politics/elections/presidential</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 23:58:57 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/new-hampshire-father-triggered-state-wide-amber-alert-found-facing-murder-childrens-mother</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/new-hampshire-father-triggered-state-wide-amber-alert-found-facing-murder-childrens-mother</guid>
                    <title>New Hampshire father who triggered state-wide Amber Alert found, facing murder of children&apos;s mother</title>
                    
                    <description>New Hampshire authorities say that the father of two young girls, who sparked an Amber Alert, has been found and charged with his wife&amp;apos;s murder.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Two young children, who prompted &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/amber-alerts-one-pops-up-phone&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;an Amber Alert&lt;/a&gt; in New Hampshire, are safe, and their father is in custody after police said he shot and killed their mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the New Hampshire Attorney General John M. Formella, 37-year-old Dustin Mark Duren was charged with second-degree murder in the death of 31-year-old Caitlyn Naffziger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said that Duren allegedly shot his wife, Naffziger, on Thursday night in the couple&apos;s shared &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/northeast/new-hampshire&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Berlin, New Hampshire&lt;/a&gt; apartment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discovery of Naffziger&apos;s body prompted state police to issue an hour-long Amber Alert for the couple&apos;s two daughters, 4-year-old Elowyn Duren and 1-year-old Vaelyn Duren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/family-70-year-old-died-punched-detroit-cop-files-50m-civil-rights-suit&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FAMILY OF 70-YEAR-OLD WHO DIED AFTER BEING PUNCHED BY DETROIT COP FILES $50M CIVIL RIGHTS SUIT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attorney General Formella said that the girls had been last seen in Berlin, New Hampshire, around 8 p.m. Thursday with their father, Duren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They said Duren &quot;may possibly be armed and dangerous,&quot; but did not offer any additional details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/kentucky-hero-who-saved-semi-truck-driver-who-was-dangling-from-bridge-identified&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KENTUCKY HERO WHO SAVED SEMI-TRUCK DRIVER WHO WAS DANGLING FROM BRIDGE IDENTIFIED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 10:30 a.m. on Friday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime/police-and-law-enforcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;New Hampshire State Police&lt;/a&gt; announced that Elowyn and Vaelyn had been found safe at an Applebee’s restaurant in Keene, which is about three hours south from Berlin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities said that Duren was taken into custody without incident at the restaurant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday evening, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Formella announced that&lt;/a&gt; the Amber Alert issued had been canceled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The Department of Justice greatly thanks the public for their assistance in this matter and their responsiveness to the alert issued earlier by the New Hampshire State Police,&quot; the attorney general said &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.doj.nh.gov/news/2024/20240301-amber-alert-cancelled.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;in a release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New Hampshire District Attorney did not immediately respond to Fox News Digital&apos;s request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/m1.png?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/png" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">8a51b1e2-b4a8-5fc7-8035-61d525707af4</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/northeast/new-hampshire</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime/homicide</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 23:53:39 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/buccaneers-star-mike-evans-plans-to-test-free-agency-for-first-time-report</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/buccaneers-star-mike-evans-plans-to-test-free-agency-for-first-time-report</guid>
                    <title>Buccaneers star Mike Evans plans to test free agency for first time: report</title>
                    
                    <description>Five-time Pro Bowl wide receiver Mike Evans is expected to officially enter the free agency market later this month after spending his entire NFL career with the Buccaneers.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;NFL star wide receiver &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/person/mike-evans&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mike Evans&lt;/a&gt; has spent his entire professional football career in one place. But, the 30-year-old&apos;s future with the Tampa Bay Buccaneers appears to be in doubt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Evans has consistently expressed his desire to stay in Tampa, he will likely explore his options on the free agent market, according to a report from The Athletic. Evans is scheduled to enter free agency later this month at the start of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/sports/nfl&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the NFL&apos;s&lt;/a&gt; new league year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evans and his representatives were believed to be working towards a contract extension, but talks with the Buccaneers have reportedly stalled. So, Evans will now listen to other teams before deciding where he will play in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports&quot; id=&quot;OWAf6c5c263-e13c-683a-7fc7-ddeedfa65589&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MORE SPORTS COVERAGE ON FOXNEWS.COM&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evans is coming off another strong season. He finished the 2023 campaign with 1,255 receiving yards and 13 touchdowns. He has never finished any of his ten NFL seasons with less than 1,000 receiving yards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports/nflpa-survey-biggest-takeaways-chiefs-big-red-wins-big-bengals-give-cincinnati-dining-0-star-rating&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NFLPA SURVEY BIGGEST TAKEAWAYS: CHIEFS’ BIG RED WINS BIG; BENGALS GIVE CINCINNATI DINING 0-STAR RATING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evans&apos; strong play carried over into the 2023 postseason. He had a combined 195 receiving yards and a touchdown in the Bucs&apos; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports/bucs-todd-bowles-ridiculed-social-media-not-using-final-timeout-loss-lions&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;two playoff games&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evans&apos; consistency, along with his intangible skills, will likely appeal to multiple NFL teams if he does end up on the open market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He agreed to a five-year contract extension with the Bucs back in 2018. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evans has 11,680 career receiving yards. He has been named to five Pro Bowls in his decade-long run with the Bucs. He is also a two-time Second-team All-Pro receiver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Pittman Jr., Marquise Brown, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports/calvin-ridley-pens-letter-after-reinstatement-i-made-the-worst-mistake-of-my-life&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Calvin Ridley&lt;/a&gt; also headline the expected wide receiver free agent class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Follow Fox News Digital’s &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FoxNewsSports_&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;sports coverage on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; and subscribe to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;the Fox News Sports Huddle newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2022/09/931/523/Mike-Evans7.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">be549aab-517c-539a-9fc6-eb74704e8972</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports/nfl/tampa-bay-buccaneers</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/mike-evans</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports/nfl</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/sports</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 23:16:44 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/kentucky-hero-who-saved-semi-truck-driver-who-was-dangling-from-bridge-identified</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/kentucky-hero-who-saved-semi-truck-driver-who-was-dangling-from-bridge-identified</guid>
                    <title>Kentucky hero who saved semi-truck driver who was dangling from bridge identified</title>
                    
                    <description>Bryce Carden has been identified as the firefighter who rescued a semi-truck driver who was stuck dangling over the Clark Memorial Bridge in Kentucky on Friday.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Following the harrowing rescue of a semi-truck driver who was stuck dangling over the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/southeast/kentucky&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clark Memorial Bridge in Kentucky&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the city&apos;s fire chief praised the first responders for their daring rescue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;All the credit goes right here,&quot; Louisville Fire Chief Brian O&apos;Neill said in a press conference Friday. &quot;These are some serious heroes. This was some really professional, well-practiced, well-trained stuff.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;These men and women make me so proud,&quot; O&apos;Neill said. &quot;This motivates the heck out of me every day.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firefighter who rappelled down to the driver and carried her to safety was identified as 29-year-old Bryce Carden, who specializes in high-angle rescues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/driver-pulled-truck-dangling-louisville-bridge-ohio-river-dramatic-rescue&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRIVER PULLED FROM TRUCK DANGLING FROM LOUISVILLE BRIDGE OVER OHIO RIVER IN DRAMATIC RESCUE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;This guy is probably one of the nicest, happiest guys that you&apos;ll ever want to meet in your life, and he is the exact right person to put down there to try to keep that patient calm,&quot; O&apos;Neill said, speaking of Carden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;O&apos;Neill said that this is a &quot;once in a career&quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/man-ejected-from-sunroof-during-big-sur-cliff-fall-waits-2-days-for-rescue&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;type of rescue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;This is very much a worse case scenario and something that you don&apos;t expect to happen,&quot; he said. &quot;This is a once in a career kind of thing.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carden said that he was not nervous because he knew that his team had his back and that the woman was calm and collected. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I was not nervous at all going over the edge because I knew that they had me on the top side. Once I reached her, she was super calm, collected and helped me do what I needed to do to get her to safety, essentially. And it all worked out for the best, and we&apos;ll go back to quarters and get ready to do it again if we have to,&quot; he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/fire-engine-plows-long-island-furniture-store-injuring-4&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FIRE ENGINE PLOWS INTO LONG ISLAND FURNITURE STORE, INJURING 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;She was praying a lot, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/faith-values/faith&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;I was praying&lt;/a&gt; right there with her,&quot; he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carden said this rescue operation &quot;tops&quot; everything else he has done so far in his career. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We&apos;ve definitely done a few crazy things, but yes, this tops it so far. Like I said, we trained for this situation probably a hundred times, but they actually put it in action. It felt good,&quot; Carden said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/disasters&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;initial crash&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; was reported around 12:15 local time on Friday afternoon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The truck was moving northbound on the bridge when it apparently crossed the lane and crashed through the bridge&apos;s guardrail, according to local reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dramatic video showed Carden being &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/video-shows-incredible-rescue-driver-trapped-semi-truck-dangling-bridge&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;lowered to the semi truck&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; from a ladder in order to lift the female driver to safety. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trailer of the truck could be seen wedged against the beams of the bridge, stopping it from falling into the water below. The hood of the truck also popped open and could be seen hanging from the truck&apos;s cab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the semi, three other vehicles - two passenger vehicles and a pickup truck - were involved in the wreck. Two people in one of those vehicles were also taken to the University of Louisville Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bridge remained closed following the rescue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bridge was built in 1929. It&apos;s four lanes, two in each direction, with a speed limit of 35 mph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fox News&apos; Michael Dorgan contributed to this report.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/f1.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">387e5b9e-939c-555c-b004-c09fc7c0cd98</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southeast/kentucky</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/disasters</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime/police-and-law-enforcement</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:33:24 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/fashion-icon-iris-apfel-dead-at-102</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/fashion-icon-iris-apfel-dead-at-102</guid>
                    <title>Fashion icon Iris Apfel dead at 102</title>
                    
                    <description>Iris Apfel, a fashion celebrity known for her eccentric style, died in her Palm Beach, Florida home on Friday, her agent said.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxbusiness.com/category/fox-news-style-and-beauty&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Iris Apfel&lt;/a&gt;, a fashion celebrity and icon known for her eccentric style, has died. She was 102.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No cause of death was given. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lori Sale, Apfel&apos;s agent, confirmed her death with The Associated Press. Her passing was also announced on her Instagram page, which had nearly 3 million followers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Iris Barrel Apfel. August 29, 1921 - March 1, 2024,&quot; the social media post stated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxbusiness.com/features/amish-inspired-urban-southern-leather-bags-brand-new-success&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMISH-INSPIRED URBAN SOUTHERN LEATHER BAGS BRAND NEW SUCCESS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She reportedly died at her Palm Beach, Florida, home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Born Aug. 29, 1921, Apfel was famous for her irreverent, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxbusiness.com/category/fox-news-style&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;eye-catching outfits&lt;/a&gt;, mixing haute couture and oversized costume jewelry. A classic Apfel look would, for instance, pair a feather boa with strands of chunky beads, bangles and a jacket decorated with Native American beadwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With her big, round, black-rimmed glasses, bright red lipstick and short white hair, she stood out at every fashion show she attended. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I&apos;m not pretty, and I&apos;ll never be pretty, but it doesn&apos;t matter,&quot; she once said. &quot;I have something much better. I have style.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/video/5841587966001&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;WORLD&apos;S MOST EXPENSIVE SHOES YOURS FOR ONLY $17 MILLION&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apfel amassed a large collection of clothing and accessories, prompting the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York to open an exhibition of her wardrobe. The exhibit, which opened in 2005, was titled: &quot;Rara Avis: Selections From the Iris Apfel Collection.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apfel was an expert on textiles and antique fabrics. She and her husband Carl owned a textile manufacturing company, Old World Weavers, and specialized in restoration work, including projects at the White House under six different U.S. presidents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her celebrity clients included Estée Lauder and Greta Garbo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In her later years, Apfel &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxbusiness.com/media&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;appeared in ads&lt;/a&gt; for brands like M.A.C. cosmetics and Kate Spade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also designed a line of accessories and jewelry for Home Shopping Network, collaborated with H&amp;amp;M on a sold-out-in-minutes collection of brightly-colored apparel, jewelry and shoes, put out a makeup line with Ciaté London, an eyeglass collection with Zenni and partnered with Ruggable on floor coverings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Associated Press contributed to this report. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/AP24062061580585.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">def4bc69-4598-51ae-845d-a13dad205528</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/entertainment/style</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/entertainment/events/obituary</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/lifestyle</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:24:21 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/jesse-watters-joe-bidens-brothers-deposition-is-even-more-preposterous-than-hunters</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/media/jesse-watters-joe-bidens-brothers-deposition-is-even-more-preposterous-than-hunters</guid>
                    <title>JESSE WATTERS: Joe Biden&apos;s brother&apos;s deposition is even more preposterous than Hunter&apos;s</title>
                    
                    <description>Jesse Watters discsses the revealing details from Jim Biden and Hunter Biden&amp;apos;s depositions on &amp;quot;Jesse Watters Primetime.&amp;quot;</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Jesse Watters discusses both Jim Biden and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-full-deposition-admits-father-speakerphone-invited-him-meetings-denies-involvement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Hunter Biden&apos;s released &lt;/a&gt;transcripts from their depositions during President Biden&apos;s impeachment inquiry on &quot;Jesse Watters Primetime.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JESSE WATTERS: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;i&gt;We just got our hands on Joe Biden&apos;s brother&apos;s deposition, and it is even more preposterous than Hunter&apos;s. And that&apos;s a high bar. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-testify-did-not-involve-father-businesses-saying-impeachment-inquiry-baseless&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HUNTER BIDEN TESTIFIES HE ‘DID NOT INVOLVE’ HIS FATHER IN HIS BUSINESSES, CALLS IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY ‘BASELESS’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;As we reported last night, not only did Hunter admit his dad is &quot;The Big Guy,&quot; but he says Joe is stopping by his business meetings that he called birthday parties to eat bowls of spaghetti with his clients. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Now, Hunter doesn&apos;t call them clients. He told congressional investigators they&apos;re really his friends. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/comer-says-impeachment-inquiry-moving-next-phase-hunter-biden-testifying-public-hearing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Hunter&apos;s friends with&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; Russians living in Moscow and the spy chief of China. His words, not mine. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What kind of business are you in when your dad keeps showing up at your business meetings, though? My dad doesn&apos;t pop into my editorial meetings at Fox and say hi to my producers. When you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-paid-100k-through-joint-venture-chinese-energy-firm-ex-associate-testified&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;take your clients&lt;/a&gt; out to lunch, does your dad stop by for spaghetti? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hunter says when he&apos;s with his business partners and his dad happens to call, he puts them on speaker. I&apos;ve never done that, pobably because my dad&apos;s not famous. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But let&apos;s say my dad was Biden. The reason I&apos;m putting my dad on the phone is to impress my partners and show them what kind of easy access they can get to dad. Biden doesn&apos;t know his cameo or his phone calls are the main course of the business dinner.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/cf-images.us-east-1.prod.boltdns.net/v1/static/694940094001/65289680-914c-4109-813b-5156095ff51a/2acee885-8874-4958-8f95-22f8bc93e937/1280x720/match/896/500/image.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="896" height="500" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">77ed5c88-5417-5112-8862-8b2c751038c9</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media/fox-news-flash</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/shows/jesse-watters-primetime</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/hunter-biden</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/joe-biden</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:22:25 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nikki-haley-gains-endorsements-moderate-gop-senators-uphill-primary-battle</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nikki-haley-gains-endorsements-moderate-gop-senators-uphill-primary-battle</guid>
                    <title>Nikki Haley gains endorsements from moderate GOP senators amid uphill primary battle</title>
                    
                    <description>GOP presidential candidate Nikki Haley has received her first two senatorial endorsements from Susan Collins and Lisa Murkowski.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/person/nikki-haley&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nikki Haley&lt;/a&gt; on Friday received endorsements from two of the GOP’s most moderate senators in Susan Collins, R-Maine, and Lisa Murkowski, R-Alaska. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collins, who previously voted to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/republican-senators-vote-to-convict-trump-on-incitement-charge&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;convict then-President Trump&lt;/a&gt; in his impeachment trial in which he was acquitted, revealed Friday that she voted for Haley in Maine’s primary this week, calling her &quot;extremely well-qualified.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;She has the energy, intellect, and temperament that we need to lead our country in these very tumultuous times,&quot; she said, according to the Bangor Daily News. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday, Murkowski also threw her support behind the former South Carolina governor, saying she was &quot;proud&quot; to endorse her. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/haley-slams-trump-for-senate-losses-calls-out-gop-lawmakers-for-courting-him&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HALEY SLAMS TRUMP FOR SENATE LOSSES, CALLS OUT GOP LAWMAKERS FOR COURTING HIM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collins and Murkowski are the only senators to endorse Haley as the rest of the party has coalesced behind Trump, including &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/tim-scott-endorsement-donald-trump-latest-sign-gop-consolidating-around-former-president&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;South Carolina Sen. Tim Scott&lt;/a&gt;, from Haley’s home state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We need a president who sees Americans as one American family, and that’s why I came to the very warm state of New Hampshire to endorse the next president of the United States, President Donald Trump,&quot; Scott said in January. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Haley has yet to win a primary or caucus, having most recently lost South Carolina 39% to Trump’s 59%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dc-primary-represents-haleys-best-chance-yet-beat-trump&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DC PRIMARY REPRESENTS HALEY&apos;S BEST CHANCE YET TO BEAT TRUMP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the 52-year-old has refused to drop out of the race, insisting Republicans need another option besides Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also claimed last week that Trump&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nikki-haley-trump-not-win-general-election-south-carolina-primary&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; would not be able&lt;/a&gt; to beat President Biden in the general election.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/download&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO GET THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Donald Trump will not win the general election. You can have him win any primary you want, he will not win a general election,&quot; she told CNN last Friday. &quot;We will have a female President of the United States: It will either be me or it will be Kamala Harris. But if Donald Trump is the nominee, you can mark my words, he will not win a general election.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/nikki-haley-2.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">db224045-8bb7-5770-873f-8145bd19c9d1</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/politics</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/nikki-haley</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/politics/elections</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/donald-trump</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/politics</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:19:58 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/sean-hannity-out-mind-amazing-achievement-hunter-biden</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/media/sean-hannity-out-mind-amazing-achievement-hunter-biden</guid>
                    <title>SEAN HANNITY: For being out of his mind, this was a pretty amazing achievement for Hunter Biden</title>
                    
                    <description>Fox News host Sean Hannity says the only things Hunter Biden can remember is that his father was not there when he was making business deals on &amp;quot;Hannity.&amp;quot;</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Fox News host Sean Hannity breaks down Hunter Biden’s deposition over his allegedly shady business dealings on &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hannity&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEAN HANNITY: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;i&gt;Now, the transcript of &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hunter-biden-full-deposition-admits-father-speakerphone-invited-him-meetings-denies-involvement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hunter Biden&apos;s deposition&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; has been released late last night, and we have been extensively combing through it. Now, according to the transcript, Hunter addressed the infamous, &quot;I&apos;m sitting here with my father,&quot; that WhatsApp message, telling lawmakers he can&apos;t even remember sending it because he was either so drunk or high, saying, &quot;I was out of my mind.&quot; The only thing that Hunter can say for sure, that he can remember, is that his father was not there.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/majority-black-panelists-north-carolina-agree-biden-economy-hurting-living-check-to-check&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MAJORITY OF BLACK PANELISTS IN NORTH CAROLINA AGREE THAT BIDEN ECONOMY IS HURTING: &apos;LIVING CHECK-TO-CHECK&apos;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Wow. How selective can one be? (Out of my mind, I don&apos;t remember even sending the text. I&apos;m not even sure if it&apos;s my text, but I know for sure my dad wasn&apos;t there.) OK. Now, just days after that threatening message was sent, according to a 2020 Senate report, in accounts linked to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/comer-says-impeachment-inquiry-moving-next-phase-hunter-biden-testifying-public-hearing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hunter Biden&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;, guess what? &lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;They received over $5 million from the CEFC. That&apos;s who he sent the WhatsApp message to. For being out of his mind, you got to admit, I&apos;d say that&apos;s a pretty amazing achievement. Hunter also confirmed to lawmakers that he did, in fact, receive money from Chinese companies. Now, this is in stark contrast from his comments during that disastrous GMA interview when he said he didn&apos;t receive one cent from China.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/1200/675/Video-59.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="1200" height="675" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">526e1aa1-b068-5dc0-92cf-448539a3d7c3</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/shows/hannity/transcript/hannitys-monologue</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/politics</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/hunter-biden</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:55:43 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/video-of-8-year-olds-national-anthem-performance-at-pacers-game-draws-millions-of-social-media-views</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/video-of-8-year-olds-national-anthem-performance-at-pacers-game-draws-millions-of-social-media-views</guid>
                    <title>Video of 8-year-old&apos;s national anthem performance at Pacers game draws millions of social media views</title>
                    
                    <description>The young performer stood at center court in an American flag dress and white gloves during Pacers-Raptors pregame inside Gainbridge Fieldhouse.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A social media video of a young girl&apos;s performance of the national anthem prior to the tipoff of a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/sports/nba/indiana-pacers&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Indiana Pacers&lt;/a&gt; game continues to draw millions of views.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kinsley Murray stood at center court inside the Pacers&apos; home arena Feb. 26 wearing a patriotic dress and white gloves and delivered her rendition of &quot;The Star-Spangled Banner.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pacers posted a video of her pregame performance on the team&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxbusiness.com/category/tiktok&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;TikTok account,&lt;/a&gt; and the video had gotten more than 23 million views and 2.2 million likes as of Friday evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; id=&quot;OWAf6c5c263-e13c-683a-7fc7-ddeedfa65589&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MORE SPORTS COVERAGE ON FOXNEWS.COM&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The passion. the outfit. this anthem performance was unmatched.&quot; the Pacers captioned &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tiktok.com/@pacers/video/7340446540705647914?embed_source=71929435%2C121374463%2C121402909%2C121351166%2C121331973%2C120811592%2C120810756%3Bnull%3Bembed_blank&amp;amp;refer=embed&amp;amp;referer_url=iframely.publishing.yahoo.net%2FISTVoNT%3Fapp%3D1%26v%3D1%26img%3D1%26lazy%3D1&amp;amp;referer_video_id=7340446540705647914&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;the post&lt;/a&gt;. Murray has performed the national anthem at hundreds of sporting events over the years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also performed &quot;O Canada&quot; before singing &quot;The Star-Spangled Banner&quot; Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A social media user identifying himself as a school teacher and Kinsley&apos;s father, Shafer Murray, said she performed at a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/sports/ncaa/washington-huskies&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Washington Huskies&lt;/a&gt; basketball game in early 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2021, Kinsley gained attention for her national anthem performance before the start of a Gonzaga women&apos;s basketball game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I love to honor our country,&quot; Kinsley, who was 6 years old at the time, told KREM-TV. &quot;The louder the roar, the better I get.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxbusiness.com/category/social-media&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The social media reaction&lt;/a&gt; to Kinsely&apos;s latest performance varied widely. Some offered their applause, while others voiced criticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some defended the young performer and pushed back against comments some viewed as negative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I watched that video and seeing all of the disgusting comments, all the hatred, all the bully comments to that girl is absolutely atrocious,&quot; TikTok user Midnight Michaelson wrote. &quot;I would like to see everybody come on here now and tell you how sorry I am and how apologetic you are for attacking this little girl.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/sports/nba/new-orleans-pelicans&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;New Orleans Pelicans&lt;/a&gt; host the Pacers Friday night. Indiana entered Friday&apos;s game seventh in the Eastern Conference standings with a 34-26 record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Follow Fox News Digital’s &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FoxNewsSports_&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;sports coverage on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; and subscribe to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;the Fox News Sports Huddle newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/Indiana-Pacers-logo.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">d8dc4058-6ab7-5c4b-ad01-cf7724f4e7f8</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports/nba/indiana-pacers</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports/nba</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/topic/trending-news</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/education/patriotism</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/sports</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:53:40 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/measles-vaccinations-given-70s-80s-may-have-worn-off-doctor-warns</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/health/measles-vaccinations-given-70s-80s-may-have-worn-off-doctor-warns</guid>
                    <title>Measles vaccinations given in &apos;70s and &apos;80s may have worn off by now, doctor warns</title>
                    
                    <description>Amid the current measles outbreak in Florida, some doctors are warning that those who got vaccinated in the 70s or 80s may not be fully protected today.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;If you were vaccinated for measles in the 1970s or &apos;80s, there’s a chance the protection has worn off by now, some doctors are warning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the current &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/science/wild-nature/viruses&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt; in Florida, USF College of Public Health associate professor Jill Roberts spoke to FOX 13 in Tampa about the possibility of legacy vaccines becoming less effective over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The measles vaccine was first introduced in 1968.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/health/measles-outbreaks-florida-department-health-speaks-against-false-information&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;AMID MEASLES OUTBREAKS, FLORIDA DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH SPEAKS OUT AGAINST ‘FALSE INFORMATION’&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three years later, in 1971, the MMR vaccine made its debut. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This combination vaccine provides a trifecta of protection against measles, mumps and rubella.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A couple of decades after the release of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease/vaccines&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt;, measles was declared eliminated in the U.S. in 2000. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who received measles vaccinations in the ‘70s and ’80s — mainly people currently in their 40s and 50s — Roberts recommends checking with a health care provider about their status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/health/measles-outbreaks-us-uk-have-health-agencies-high-alert-be-vigilant&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MEASLES OUTBREAKS IN US, UK HAVE HEALTH AGENCIES ON HIGH ALERT: ‘BE VIGILANT’&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;There&apos;s absolutely no risk in getting another MMR, so if you don&apos;t know, just go get another shot,&quot; she advised. &quot;They&apos;re inexpensive and widely available.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles is a highly contagious virus for those who have not &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;previously been infected&lt;/a&gt; or vaccinated, Roberts warned — with up to a 90% chance of transmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jacob Glanville, a virology expert and founder of Centivax, a San Francisco pharmaceutical company, warned about recent outbreaks in under-vaccinated communities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;If you have ever received the MMR vaccine, you likely still have immunity, although &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/healthy-living/health-care&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;talk to your doctor&lt;/a&gt; about a measles titer test if you have concerns,&quot; he told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP FOR OUR HEALTH NEWSLETTER&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The titer test measures an individual’s level of immunity to the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Marc Siegel, clinical professor of medicine at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/northeast/new-york&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;NYU Langone Medical Center&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and a Fox News medical contributor, emphasized the importance of measles vaccinations — &quot;particularly with the amount of circulating measles virus and underimmunized people coming into the U.S. at a time when there is a big measles surge around the world.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;This is not yet an official suggestion anywhere, but I do check measles titers in many of my patients, and if they are low, I may give a booster as a precaution,&quot; he told Fox News Digital.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The protection from the original vaccines may wear off over time.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Feb. 29, a total of 41 measles cases had been reported by 16 jurisdictions: Arizona, California, Florida, Georgia, Indiana, Louisiana, Maryland, Michigan, Minnesota, Missouri, New Jersey, New York City, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Washington, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/health&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more Health articles, visit &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.foxnews/health&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;www.foxnews.com/health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/10/931/523/measles-split.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">e56e0fe1-46d4-5e8c-8b04-cf062a665c7d</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/health</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/health/infectious-disease</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/science/wild-nature/viruses</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/health/infectious-disease/vaccines</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/lifestyle</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/health/healthy-living/health-care</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/health</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:45 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/south-carolina-woman-accused-killing-bride-dui-crash-released-jail-less-year</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/south-carolina-woman-accused-killing-bride-dui-crash-released-jail-less-year</guid>
                    <title>South Carolina woman accused of killing bride in DUI crash released from jail less than a year later</title>
                    
                    <description>Jamie Komoroski spent less than a year in jail after she allegedly killed a bride in a DUI crash while she was driving twice the legal speed last year.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/southeast/south-carolina&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;South Carolina&lt;/a&gt; woman who was charged with killing a bride on her wedding night in a DUI crash last April has been released from jail less than a year later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Komoroski, 26, posted her $150,000 bail on Friday, and was released from the Charleston County jail at 3:16 p.m., jail records showed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 28, 2023, Samantha Miller, 34, died and her groom, Aric Hutchinson, 36, was seriously injured, when Komoroski allegedly rear-ended their golf cart while she was driving twice the posted speed limit after the blissful newlyweds left their reception in Folly Beach, South Carolina, under a canopy of sparklers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Komoroski, whose blood-alcohol content was more than three times the legal limit, had previously been held without bail after the wreck. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/virginia-woman-bites-officer-grabs-police-firearm-flipping-car-suspected-dui-crash-authorities&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VIRGINIA WOMAN BITES OFFICER, GRABS POLICE FIREARM AFTER FLIPPING CAR IN SUSPECTED DUI CRASH: AUTHORITIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;She didn’t just kill my child,&quot; Lisa Miller, the bride’s mother, told the court last year while arguing that Komoroski didn&apos;t deserve to be released. &quot;She killed all of us.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Komoroski will be fitted with a SCRAM ankle monitor, jail records showed. The monitor measures the wearer’s alcohol level by sampling their sweat every 30 minutes, according to its website. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was also forced to surrender her passport and cannot drive and is not allowed to leave her home except for medical emergencies or court dates, according to the New York Post. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A judge ruled previously that she could be allowed bond if her trial didn’t start before this March. Her trial date hasn’t been set. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/sc-judge-denies-bond-woman-accused-killing-bride-wedding-night-dwi-crash&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SC JUDGE DENIES BOND FOR WOMAN IN DWI CRASH THAT KILLED BRIDE AS GRIEVING MOTHER SAYS SHE ‘KILLED ALL OF US’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I want that to include house arrest, ankle monitoring and not being able to leave the state,&quot; Miller told the Post. &quot;We were all expecting she would have been bonded out first time [last summer] but luckily the judge kept her in, I think that was to do with our impact statements.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Komoroski’s lawyer told the Post: &quot;She now looks forward to demonstrating her continued commitment to rehabilitation upon her pretrial release from detention,&quot; adding that she isn’t a flight risk or danger to the community. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Komoroski has been charged with three counts of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;felony DUI &lt;/a&gt;resulting in death and one count of reckless homicide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/south-carolina-groom-planning-brides-funeral-wedding-day-crash&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;night of the fatal crash&lt;/a&gt;, Komoroski drank &quot;copious amounts of alcohol&quot; while barhopping with friends, the groom alleged in a civil wrongful death lawsuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/download&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO GET THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to an affidavit obtained by Fox News Digital, Komoroski refused to take a sobriety test at the scene and appeared &quot;very unsteady on her feet and almost fell down.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moments before Komoroski allegedly plowed into the couple in her Toyota Camry, Miller told her new husband she wanted the &quot;night to last forever.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/south-carolina-husband-recalls-moment-learned-bride-dead&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Hutchinson suffered&lt;/u&gt; &lt;/a&gt;brain bleeding, broken bones and facial fractures that have required numerous surgeries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fox News Digital&apos;s Rebecca Rosenberg contributed to this report. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2023/05/931/523/Samantha-Miller-Jamie-Lee-Komoro-DUI-Death.jpeg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">937bdcb7-3629-5f20-bd05-4c6354b2fe9d</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southeast/south-carolina</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:01:08 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/cnns-christiane-amanpour-grilled-bosses-networks-double-standards-israel-coverage-report</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/media/cnns-christiane-amanpour-grilled-bosses-networks-double-standards-israel-coverage-report</guid>
                    <title>CNN&apos;s Christiane Amanpour grilled bosses over network&apos;s &apos;double standards&apos; on Israel coverage: Report</title>
                    
                    <description>The Intercept reported on a tense meeting that took place between CNN&amp;apos;s top brass and journalists at the network&amp;apos;s London bureau including veteran anchor Christiane Amanpour.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Veteran CNN journalist Christian Amanpour reportedly confronted her new boss Mark Thompson and other executives over what she says are &quot;double standards&quot; when it came to the network&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/world/world-regions/israel&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Israel-Hamas coverage&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday, &lt;a href=&quot;https://theintercept.com/2024/03/01/cnn-christiane-amanpour-israel-gaza-coverage/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Intercept reported&lt;/a&gt; on an internal meeting at CNN&apos;s London bureau last month that got tense while discussing the network&apos;s protocols for covering the ongoing war and the alleged &quot;hostile climate for Arab reporters.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recurring issue among the CNN journalists attending the meeting was the process of running their reporting through CNN&apos;s &quot;SecondEyes&quot; verifying program at the network&apos;s Jerusalem bureau, which according to The Intercept&apos;s report &quot;slows down reporting on Gaza and filters news about the war through journalists in Jerusalem who operate under the shadow of Israel&apos;s military censor.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;You’ve heard from me, you’ve heard my, you know, real distress with SecondEyes — changing copy, double standards, and all the rest,&quot; Amanpour said, according to a leaked recording of the meeting. &quot;So you’ve heard it, and I hear what your response is and I hope it does go a long way.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/cnns-amanpour-says-rest-world-agrees-queen-jordan-one-sided-support-israel&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNN&apos;S AMANPOUR SAYS ‘REST OF THE WORLD&apos; AGREES WITH QUEEN OF JORDAN THAT THERE IS ONE-SIDED SUPPORT FOR ISRAEL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several staffers reportedly panned CNN&apos;s coverage of the war, saying it has &quot;weakened the network’s standing in the region and has led Arab staffers… feeling as though their lives are expendable.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I was in southern Lebanon during October and November… And it was more distressing for me to turn on CNN, than the bombs falling nearby,&quot; one CNN journalist told their bosses. &quot;I find that my colleagues, my family, are platforming people over and over again, that are either calling for my death, or using very dehumanizing language against me … and people that look like me. And obviously, this has a huge impact in our credibility in the region.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That journalist then asked Thompson directly, &quot;What have you done, and what are you doing to address the hate speech that fills our air and informed our coverage, especially in the first few months of the war?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/ex-israeli-pm-rejects-cnns-tapper-pressing-him-gaza-civilian-deaths&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EX-ISRAELI PM REJECTS CNN&apos;S TAPPER PRESSING HIM ON GAZA CIVILIAN DEATHS: HAMAS IS ‘PLACING THEM IN HARM’S WAY&apos;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to The Intercept, Thompson initially responded by touting CNN&apos;s coverage of the war, though he added &quot;it is impossible to do this kind of story where there are people with incredibly strong opinions on both sides&quot; without &quot;sometimes making mistakes.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I think the fact that it’s been very difficult for us until relatively recently, and even today, to get fully on the ground inside Gaza, has made it hard for us to deliver the kind of individualized personal stories of what it’s been like for the people of Gaza, in the way it has been more possible for us with the story of the families of those murdered and kidnapped by Hamas in the original Hamas attack on Israel,&quot; Thompson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thompson went on to insist CNN would give the &quot;same&quot; sympathetic coverage to the victims in Gaza as the families of Israeli hostages if it didn&apos;t have access restraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I think that we have for the most part tried very hard to capture the … our job is not to be moral arbiters, it is to report what’s happening,&quot; Thompson told staff. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/legacy-media-decries-bothsidesism-except-israel-hamas&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;THE LEGACY MEDIA DECRIES ‘BOTHSIDESISM’ EXCEPT WHEN IT INVOLVES ISRAEL AND HAMAS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A separate CNN staffer complained how &quot;very senior anchors&quot; are not challenging Israeli officials enough on air and that CNN&apos;s Muslim and Arab journalists are &quot;made to feel that they must denounce Hamas to clear their names and be taken seriously as journalists.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I’ve heard this, where a number of younger colleagues now feel that they didn’t want to put their hands up to speak up even in the kind of the local Bureau meeting,&quot; the staffer told Thompson. &quot;People were taking their names off bylines.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per The Intercept, &quot;Thompson interjected, saying that people seemed to be speaking up now and that he welcomes editorial discussions. Another staffer disputed that characterization and noted that Arab and Muslim journalists walk a difficult line between feeling proud of working for CNN while facing pressure from their families and communities over working for a network with a pronounced pro-Israel bias.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amanpour also urged Thompson to have &quot;experts&quot; of the region to be reporting on the ground, telling him &quot;It isn’t a place, with due respect, to send people who we want to promote or whatever, or teach. Maybe in the second wave, maybe in the third wave — but in the first wave, it has to be the people who know, through experience, what they’re seeing, and how to speak truth to power on all sides. And how to recognize the difference between political or whatever or terrorist attack, and the humanity, and to be able to put all of that into reporting.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;For me, video is not a talking head on a balcony in a capital. It just isn’t. To me, video is reportage,&quot; she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson for CNN declined to comment to Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amanpour certainly isn&apos;t afraid to speak her mind to her bosses. Last year, she &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media/cnns-christiane-amanpour-calls-out-boss-chris-licht-offers-stunning-rebuke-trump-town-hall&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;confronted ousted CNN honcho Chris Licht&lt;/a&gt; over her disapproval of the network&apos;s handling of the Trump town hall. &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/AmanpourThompson.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">ac22af0e-e67d-5148-91ed-dc57738f0567</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/world-regions/israel</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media/culture-trends</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/world-regions/middle-east</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:00:33 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/laura-ingraham-get-trump-express-derailment</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/media/laura-ingraham-get-trump-express-derailment</guid>
                    <title>LAURA INGRAHAM: The &apos;Get Trump&apos; express may be headed for a derailment</title>
                    
                    <description>&amp;quot;The Ingraham Angle&amp;quot; host Laura Ingraham reacts to federal judge Aileen Cannon pushing back on Special Counsel Jack Smith&amp;apos;s July trial date in the classified documents case against former President Trump.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Fox News host Laura Ingraham reacts to efforts at &quot;keeping Trump in a courtroom&quot; ahead of the 2024 election Friday on &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/shows/ingraham-angle&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Ingraham Angle&lt;/a&gt;.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/special-counsel-jack-smith-proposes-new-date-trump-classified-records-trial&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPECIAL COUNSEL JACK SMITH PROPOSES NEW DATE FOR TRUMP CLASSIFIED RECORDS TRIAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LAURA INGRAHAM: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;i&gt;At a morning hearing in the classified docs case against President Trump. Federal Judge Aileen Cannon signaled that Jack Smith suggested the July trial date would be a no-go because the trial time frame for all the motion work that has to be done would be far too compressed. That totally makes sense. Of course, &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trumps-lawyers-push-dismissal-classified-documents-case-arguing-presidential-immunity&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Trump&apos;s lawyers&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; want this travesty to be postponed until after the election. Or I have an idea. How about holding off until and unless Joe Biden is brought up on charges for his own concealment of government records? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;All right. Meanwhile, not a good idea to keep digging when you&apos;re already sinking, but that&apos;s what Smith&apos;s office did when his associate intimated that the judge wasn&apos;t moving quickly enough. To which she tersely replied: &quot;I can assure you that, in [the] building, there&apos;s a good deal of judicial work going on.&quot; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Oh, now, our reporters, David Spunt and Jake Gibson are reporting that if they had to choose a date for the federal appeal, &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/special-counsel-jack-smith-proposes-new-date-trump-classified-records-trial&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Trump&apos;s legal team&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; said they could do August 12th to avoid running right up into the election. Of course, if a trial takes, let&apos;s say, six weeks, which is what they&apos;re projecting, keeping Trump in a courtroom now, that&apos;s the ultimate in election interference, isn&apos;t it? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;But clearly this guy just doesn&apos;t care. He&apos;s willing to dispense with the DOJ manual that highly discourages bringing cases against candidates that would impact the election because of the timing. It&apos;s a so-called 60-day rule, even though it doesn&apos;t mention 60 days, of course. Smith&apos;s office says that they&apos;re in compliance, but really, they&apos;re willing to skirt the recommendations because, after all, there&apos;s always a Trump exemption. Now, regardless of when the trial starts, Trump&apos;s legal team has played this smartly so far in Judge Cannon&apos;s concern about the unfairness of a rush schedule.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/cf-images.us-east-1.prod.boltdns.net/v1/static/694940094001/1543ea75-7e22-4b98-8984-a50d534cd3bc/193f1dd1-afae-4c48-a48a-f953d1f9b212/1280x720/match/896/500/image.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="896" height="500" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">52d00d34-5a05-55ca-b31b-4c3b7c1ee6f2</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media/fox-news-flash</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/shows/ingraham-angle</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:49:34 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/jake-paul-opponents-fans-exchange-explicit-chants-weigh-in</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/jake-paul-opponents-fans-exchange-explicit-chants-weigh-in</guid>
                    <title>Jake Paul and his opponent&apos;s fans exchange explicit chants at weigh-in</title>
                    
                    <description>Ahead of his fight against Ryan Bourland in Puerto Rico, Jake Paul and fans of &amp;quot;The Rhino&amp;quot; exchanged chants filled with F-bombs at Friday&amp;apos;s weigh-in.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico — &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/person/jake-paul&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jake Paul&lt;/a&gt; put on a show before the show for several hundred at Friday night’s weigh-in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul will face his most experienced opponent, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/sports/boxing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ryan Bourland&lt;/a&gt;, in Puerto Rico Saturday night .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicknamed &quot;The Rhino,&quot; Bourland is a former Golden Gloves champion with 19 pro fights under his belt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bourland has a career record of 17-2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MORE SPORTS COVERAGE ON FOXNEWS.COM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul has made Puerto Rico home in recent years, crediting the island for his boxing success and saying he’s been able to train more diligently and lock in more easily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he didn’t exactly have much of a home ring advantage at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/us-puerto-rico&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Distrito T-Mobile in San Juan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plenty of Rhino supporters were in the crowd, some chanting &quot;F--- Jake Paul&quot; when he entered the stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So Paul, a master of the troll, egged them on in response. When asked by reporter Ariel Helwani about his emotions, he chanted his response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;F--- the Rhino,&quot; he sang several times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bourland supporters responded with a &quot;F—- Jake Paul&quot; chant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Paul had the final word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I&apos;m sick of these dumba-- rhinos walking around this motherf---ing island. Tomorrow, the rhinos are going extinct. I promise you that.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports/jake-paul-basically-never-ending-machine-reason&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JAKE PAUL IS ‘BASICALLY A NEVER-ENDING MACHINE’ FOR THIS REASON&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Thursday’s press conference, Paul even joked about the nickname, saying Bourland didn’t &quot;embody the true rhino spirit&quot; after Bourland said he is not vegan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point, Helwani asked Bourland if he felt Paul respects him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;It don&apos;t matter,&quot; Bourland replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul is coming off a fight that didn&apos;t last a single round. On Dec. 15, he knocked out Andre August and waved goodbye to him on the mat. That fight improved his professional record to 8-1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saturday will mark Bourland&apos;s first fight since Sept. 17, 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow Fox News Digital’s &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FoxNewsSports_&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sports coverage on X&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt; and subscribe to &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the Fox News Sports Huddle newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/jake-paul-ryan-bourland.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">2c409705-ef81-5a41-9b28-f5b44e57c572</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/jake-paul</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports/boxing</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/sports</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/cambodias-pioneering-post-khmer-rouge-era-phnom-penh-post-newspaper-stop-print-publication</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/world/cambodias-pioneering-post-khmer-rouge-era-phnom-penh-post-newspaper-stop-print-publication</guid>
                    <title>Cambodia&apos;s pioneering post-Khmer Rouge era Phnom Penh Post newspaper will stop print publication</title>
                    
                    <description>The Phnom Penh Post, which evolved into a bilingual institution, publishing in both Khmer and English daily, has announced it will cease its print operations.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;PHNOM PENH, Cambodia (AP) — The Phnom Penh Post, a newspaper founded in 1992 as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/world/cambodias-new-prime-minister-appoints-youngest-brother-deputy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Cambodia&lt;/a&gt; sought to re-establish stability and democracy after decades of war and unrest, said Friday that it will stop publishing in print this month, the latest blow to the country&apos;s dwindling independent media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Post was founded as an English-language biweekly in 1992. It later added a Khmer-language edition, and in 2008 began publishing daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/world/2-anti-government-activists-cambodia-charged-insulting-king-social-media&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2 ANTI-GOVERNMENT ACTIVISTS IN CAMBODIA CHARGED WITH INSULTING KING ON SOCIAL MEDIA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wrote on social media accounts that it would stop publishing both English and Khmer editions by March 29, citing a decline in advertising revenues due to a pandemic-related economic downturn, which added to financial difficulties caused by the spread of social media and other new technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although not mentioned in the announcement, Ly Tayseng, the Post&apos;s current CEO and publisher, confirmed in a text message to The Associated Press that it will continue publishing online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government of then-Prime Minister Hun Sen cracked down heavily on independent media in 2017. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/world/leader-cambodias-buddhist-community-tep-vong-dies-93&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Cambodia&lt;/a&gt; Daily, a competitor of the Post, was forced to close when it was presented with a huge tax bill which it felt was presented for political reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Post came under similar political pressure as it also lagged in advertising revenue, and in 2018 was sold by its Australian publisher to a Malaysian investor who was widely seen as acting as a proxy for the interests of the ruling Cambodia People’s Party. Several senior staff resigned and it ceased most of the sort of aggressive independent reporting that had once been its hallmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Post was founded on a shoestring by Americans Michael Hayes and Kathleen O’Keefe as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/world/united-nations-group-urges-cambodia-release-cambodian-american-human-rights-activist&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Cambodia&lt;/a&gt; with U.N. help, sought to recover from the devastation wrought by the brutal rule of the Khnmer Rouge in the late 1970s. The Khmer Rouge still posed a military threat into the late 1990s, and much of the early coverage focused on that conflict, aided by a multinational staff and freelancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its journalism flourished, in competition from The Cambodia Daily, founded in 1993 and also heavily staffed by young Westerners. Both papers served as a sort of training ground for young journalists early in their careers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Post, which was never very profitable, was sold by its founders to an Australia-led media group in 2008. By that time, all independent media was coming under increasing pressure as then-Prime Minister Hun Sen and his Cambodia People’s Party tightened their grip on power and sought to silence most critics. Hun Sen stepped down last year after 38 years as prime minister and was succeeded by his son, Hun Manet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, one of Cambodia&apos;s few remaining independent media outlets, Voice of Democracy radio, ceased operations after Hun Sen ordered its closure for allegedly slandering his son in a story.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/Cambodia-Newspaper.gif" type="image/gif" expression="full" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">c26348a7-b80c-596c-bc65-ab423b345229</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/world-regions/asia</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/topic/associated-press</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/world-politics</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/world</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:36:57 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/defense-attorney-slams-florida-sheriff-after-charges-dismissed-for-illegal-migrant-accused-deputy-death</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/defense-attorney-slams-florida-sheriff-after-charges-dismissed-for-illegal-migrant-accused-deputy-death</guid>
                    <title>Defense attorney slams Florida sheriff after charges dismissed for illegal migrant accused in deputy death</title>
                    
                    <description>The charges against Virgilio Aguilar Mendez, the 19-year-old illegal migrant accused of causing the death of a Florida sheriff&amp;apos;s office sergeant has had his charges dropped.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The high-profile lawyer for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/immigration/illegal-immigrants&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;an illegal migrant&lt;/a&gt; from Guatemala slammed Florida police after his client&apos;s charges were dismissed in the manslaughter of a police deputy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virgilio Aguilar Mendez, 19, was charged with aggravated manslaughter of an officer after a scuffle involving several &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime/police-and-law-enforcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;law enforcement officers&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in May 2023 left Sgt. Michael Kunovich of the St. Johns County Sheriff&apos;s Office dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday, Aguilar Mendez&apos;s charges were dropped, but the teen remains in federal custody in Florida and faces deportation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Recent expert testimony regarding the defendant’s inability to comprehend the English language, his cultural background and concerns about his intellectual capacity have raised significant issues to consider in the case,&quot; the 7th District State Attorney&apos;s Office said in a statement. &quot;Furthermore, based on the court’s recent ruling that the defendant is incompetent to proceed based on that expert testimony, dismissal of the charges is appropriate. Arrest and time served is sufficient.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/migrant-charged-deputys-death-files-civil-rights-lawsuit-cites-disability-not-knowing-english&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MIGRANT CHARGED IN DEPUTY&apos;S DEATH FILES CIVIL LAWSUIT, CITES ‘DISABILITY’ OF NOT KNOWING ENGLISH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the ruling, Aguilar Mendez&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/southeast/florida&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;attorney, Jose Baez,&lt;/a&gt; blasted the St. Johns County Sheriff&apos;s Office for &quot;creating a false narrative&quot; that the teen &quot;failed to follow instructions.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baez said that Aguilar Mendez primarily spoke Mam, a Guatemalan language, and is not competent in English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Culture that starts and ends with the sheriff, who not only doubled down and tripled down by creating a false narrative that this young man, who came in at 17, was someone who failed to follow instructions,&quot; Baez said in a press conference following Aguilar Mendez&apos;s dismissal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;He says if he only followed instructions Kunovich would still be alive,&quot; Baez said. &quot;I want to one day see him comply to orders given to him in Mam or Spanish and I would guarantee you that he would not comply. Then claim Vergilio Aguilar Mendez was going to use a knife, knowing that was a lie,&quot; Baez said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dismissal comes nine months after Kunovich, 52, collapsed from &quot;medical distress&quot; during the encounter with Aguilar Mendez, who was 18 at the time. The officer later died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the St. Johns County Sheriff’s Office, Kunovich initially approached Aguilar Mendez about 9 p.m. on May 19, suspecting him of a crime. Aguilar Mendez then continued walking away from the deputy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Aguilar Mendez was walking on a public sidewalk and speaking with his mother, which is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;not a crime,&quot;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the lawsuit states. &quot;When Sgt. Kunovich seized Aguilar Mendez, he stopped and did not try to flee.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/migrant-initially-accused-gang-attack-nypd-officers-charges-dropped-being-exonerated-da&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MIGRANT INITIALLY ACCUSED IN GANG ATTACK ON NYPD OFFICERS HAS CHARGES DROPPED AFTER BE ‘EXONERATED’: DA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The officer pursued Aguilar Mendez, who apologized in English, before continuing to resist the arrest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The migrant was allegedly confused and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime/police-and-law-enforcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;told the deputy&lt;/a&gt;: &quot;I&apos;m sorry, no speak, no speak English.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other deputies, including those who spoke Spanish, responded to the scene, which ultimately saw the officers tase the migrant and tackle him to the ground, Sheriff Robert Hardwick said at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sheriff’s office said the deputies attempted to restrain Aguilar Mendez, who they claim was resisting arrest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;While fighting on the ground, the suspect attempted to grab Sergeant Kunovich’s taser and continued to violently resist for approximately 6 minutes and 19 seconds,&quot; Hardwick said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deputies then &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;handcuffed the migrant&lt;/a&gt;, but he managed to acquire a small pocketknife. The office did not say if the migrant attempted to use the weapon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Sergeant Kunovich collapsed moments after the subject was disarmed and relentless lifesaving measures were initiated by St. Johns County Fire Rescue and Flagler Health+ personnel. He was ultimately pronounced deceased shortly after transport to Flagler Hospital,&quot; the statement continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/minnesota-shooting-2-police-officers-paramedic-killed-responding-burnsville-domestic-call-identified&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MINNESOTA SHOOTING: 2 POLICE OFFICERS, PARAMEDIC KILLED RESPONDING TO BURNSVILLE DOMESTIC CALL IDENTIFIED&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baez claims that his client was confused and was &quot;unable to understand the brutality of the officers.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scuffle was recorded by the officers’ bodycams and the lawyers point to the video as evidence of the migrant’s inability to understand or speak English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Without question, Aguilar Mendez did not understand the purpose or reason for the officers to pile on him, to physically strike him multiple times, and the repeated use of a taser by Sgt. Kunovich,&quot; Baez said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lawsuit from Baez claimed that Lt. Jose Jimenez, another responding deputy, did not make Aguilar Mendez aware of his &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/personal-freedoms/bill-of-rights&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Miranda rights&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or attempt to obtain an interpreter for him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deputies &quot;knew there was a substantial likelihood that Aguilar Mendez would be unable to communicate effectively, absent any interpretive aid for Mam, and ignored Aguilar Mendez’s statutory rights and SJCSO’s policies regarding limited English proficiency,&quot; the lawsuit reads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kunovich was a 25-year veteran of the St. Johns County Sheriff&apos;s Office and Sheriff Hardwick described him as a &quot;valued member of the St. Johns County Office who passionately dedicated his career to keeping our community safe.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The St. John&apos;s Sheriffs Department and Jose Baez were not immediately available for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fox News&apos; Lawrence Richard contributed to this report.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/02/931/523/GettyImages-1731158838.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">600fafb4-b625-5d15-b237-80af78ead42d</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/immigration/illegal-immigrants</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southeast/florida</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 20:16:17 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/dutch-forces-deployed-caribbean-territory-hit-major-oil-spill</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/world/dutch-forces-deployed-caribbean-territory-hit-major-oil-spill</guid>
                    <title>Dutch forces deployed to Caribbean territory hit by major oil spill</title>
                    
                    <description>Dutch armed forces have been deployed to the Caribbean island territory of Bonaire, with Amsterdam intent on cleaning oil from beaches impacted by a spill hundreds of miles away.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Armed forces from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/world/world-regions/europe&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the Netherlands&lt;/a&gt; have been deployed to the Dutch Caribbean island of Bonaire to clear beaches of oil coming from an offshore spill blamed on an overturned barge hundreds of miles away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The military cleaned up several beaches on the island that were reopened to the public on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The situation seems to be under control,&quot; acting Lt. Gov. Reynolds Oleana said Thursday. &quot;It remains to be seen what will happen in the coming days.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/world/trinidad-and-tobago-facing-national-emergency-major-coastal-oil-spill&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO FACING &apos;NATIONAL EMERGENCY&apos; AFTER MAJOR COASTAL OIL SPILL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmental officials said they can start assessing the damage once the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/science/planet-earth/pollution&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;polluted areas&lt;/a&gt; have been cleaned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spill occurred last month near Trinidad and Tobago and prompted officials there to declare a national emergency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government of the twin-island nation said earlier this week that a minimum of 420,000 gallons of oil mixed with water has been vacuumed from nearby waters. They warn the number is likely larger since it does not include &quot;a substantial amount&quot; of oil that traveled across the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/world/world-regions/caribbean-region&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Caribbean Sea&lt;/a&gt; or that was picked up with sand and sargassum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A preliminary investigation has found that the overturned barge had departed from Panama and was being tugged to nearby Guyana when it began to sink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The owner of the barge has not been found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials in Tobago have warned that the spill would take up to eight months to be fully cleaned, and that remediation efforts including repopulating ecosystems would take up to three years.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/02/931/523/trinidad_oil_spill.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">0c2eae0f-ea37-5717-95e8-724c6ed4c2c7</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/world-regions/caribbean-region</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/topic/associated-press</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/disasters</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/environment</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/science/planet-earth/pollution</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/world-regions/europe</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/world</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:54:22 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/tennessee-man-jailed-using-spotlight-hunt-deer-threatening-landowner</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/tennessee-man-jailed-using-spotlight-hunt-deer-threatening-landowner</guid>
                    <title>Tennessee man jailed for using spotlight to hunt deer, threatening landowner</title>
                    
                    <description>A Tennessee man has been sentenced to jailtime and issued a lifetime hunting ban over the illegal poaching of 15 deer and threats he made to a landowner whose property he hunted on.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/southeast/tennessee&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tennessee man&lt;/a&gt; was sentenced to jail and barred for life from hunting in the state after he illegally killed 15 deer over more than three years and threatened a landowner with a gun while poaching deer on his property, wildlife officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man pleaded guilty Feb. 22 in east Tennessee&apos;s Hawkins County to aggravated assault, using a spotlight to kill deer, hunting from a motor vehicle and hunting big game during a closed season, the Tennessee Wildlife Resources Agency said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In August, he and another person were hunting from a road in Rogersville and used a spotlight to kill a doe and a seven-point buck from a vehicle during the closed deer hunting season. When confronted by a landowner, the man pointed a gun at him and threatened to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime/homicide&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;kill him&lt;/a&gt;, the agency said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/pennsylvania-man-convicted-using-drone-help-hunters-find-deer-carcasses&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PENNSYLVANIA MAN CONVICTED OF USING DRONE TO HELP HUNTERS FIND DEER CARCASSES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were later stopped by a sheriff’s deputy and found to have a spotlight and hunting rifles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using a spotlight to hunt deer at night is illegal in Tennessee. The practice involves shining an artificial light at deer, which causes them to stay still as they stare at the light, the agency said. That allows the hunter to shoot at the deer before it runs away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The state also bars people from shooting at, catching or killing any animal from from a public road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After he pleaded guilty last week, the Whitesburg man was ordered to serve six months of a four-year sentence for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;aggravated assault charge&lt;/a&gt;, and six months for each of the hunting big game in closed season charges. The sentences will run at the same time, the agency said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to fines and court costs, he must pay $12,500 in restitution and had his hunting privileges revoked for life, the agency said. He also forfeited a spotlight, a muzzleloader, a rifle, and a compound bow along with deer meat, turkey parts and 14 sets of deer antlers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also had a previous poaching conviction in 2021 for spotlighting, hunting from a public roadway, and hunting deer during the closed season in Greene County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over 3 1/2 years, the man &quot;was charged with killing or assisting in killing 15 deer illegally, and admitted to poaching 20 deer from the road in 2020 alone,&quot; wildlife officer Justin Pinkston said in a statement. &quot;Sadly, most of these deer were left lying and were never recovered.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/deer_skulls_tn.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">2bac6c27-0963-55a5-822e-d9dea09d4543</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southeast/tennessee</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/topic/associated-press</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southeast</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/great-outdoors/hunting</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:44:20 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/family-70-year-old-died-punched-detroit-cop-files-50m-civil-rights-suit</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/family-70-year-old-died-punched-detroit-cop-files-50m-civil-rights-suit</guid>
                    <title>Family of 70-year-old who died after being punched by Detroit cop files $50M civil rights suit</title>
                    
                    <description>The family of 70-year-old Daryl Vance, who died after being punched by former Detroit police officer Juwan Brown, is suing the officer and the city for $50 million.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The family of a 70-year-old man who died after a Detroit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime/police-and-law-enforcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;police officer&lt;/a&gt; punched him in the face, causing him to fall to the ground, is suing the former officer and the city of Detroit, seeking $50 million for alleged civil rights violations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal lawsuit filed Thursday on behalf of Daryl Vance&apos;s family names former Detroit police officer Juwan Brown, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/detroit&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;city of Detroit&lt;/a&gt; and Detroit Police Sgt. Jarmiare McEntire as defendants, The Detroit News reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors who charged Brown last year in Vance&apos;s death have said he punched the Detroit man during a confrontation following the officer’s response to a call of a disorderly person outside a bowling alley on Sept. 1, 2023. Vance fell to the ground, hit his head and died in a hospital three weeks later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/us/suv-crashes-suburban-detroit-walmart-injuring-5&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUV CRASHES INTO SUBURBAN DETROIT WALMART, INJURING AT LEAST 5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors said the Wayne County medical examiner’s office determined that Vance’s death was caused by blunt force trauma to his head from the punch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Police brutality has no place in our society. What former Officer Brown did to Mr. Vance was nothing short of reckless and malicious police brutality,&quot; James Harrington, one of the attorneys who filed the lawsuit, said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brown was later fired from the Detroit Police Department, his attorney has said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lawsuit alleges McEntire violated Vance’s civil rights the day after the assault &quot;by conducting an illegal, warrantless search of his apartment on Sept. 2, 2023, under the guise of an investigation, where no exception to the warrant requirement to the Fourth Amendment to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/constitution&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;United States Constitution&lt;/a&gt; existed.’&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The complaint seeks $50 million in damages for alleged civil rights violations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Detroit Corporation Counsel Conrad Mallett declined to comment, citing the city’s policy of not discussing ongoing litigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A message seeking comment from Brown&apos;s attorney, Steve Fishman, was left Friday afternoon by The Associated Press.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In connection with Vance&apos;s death, Brown, 29, was charged in December 2023 with manslaughter, but a judge dismissed the charges in January, cited insufficient evidence during a preliminary hearing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wayne County prosecutors appealed the judge&apos;s ruling on Feb. 2.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2022/08/931/523/detroit-police-car.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">476831dd-7881-555e-b4d3-75df6afc41b2</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/midwest/michigan</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/topic/associated-press</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/detroit</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/midwest</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime/police-and-law-enforcement</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:42:25 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/missouri-gov-shortens-sentence-ex-chiefs-coach-britt-reid-remaining-sentence-converted-to-house-arrest</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/sports/missouri-gov-shortens-sentence-ex-chiefs-coach-britt-reid-remaining-sentence-converted-to-house-arrest</guid>
                    <title>Missouri governor reduces sentence of ex-Chiefs coach Britt Reid; remaining sentence changed to house arrest</title>
                    
                    <description>Britt Reid, the son of longtime Chiefs coach Andy Reid, previously pleaded guilty to a felony charge of driving while intoxicated. He was sentenced to three years in prison.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Missouri Gov. Mike Parson reduced the prison sentence for former &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/sports/nfl/kansas-city-chiefs&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kansas City Chiefs&lt;/a&gt; assistant coach Britt Reid, who pleaded guilty to driving while intoxicated in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drunken driving crash left a 5-year-old girl with a traumatic brain injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britt, the son of Chiefs head coach Andy Reid, will be released and serve the remainder of his &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports/ex-chiefs-coach-britt-reid-sentenced-three-years-jail-2021-car-crash&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;three-year prison sentence&lt;/a&gt; on house arrest due to the commutation, the governor&apos;s office confirmed. His sentence ends Oct. 31.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He will have to adhere to multiple conditions during his house arrest. He will be required to attend weekly meetings with a parole officer and peer support sponsor. He will also have to participate in behavioral counseling, among other conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports&quot; id=&quot;OWAf6c5c263-e13c-683a-7fc7-ddeedfa65589&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MORE SPORTS COVERAGE ON FOXNEWS.COM&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reid was sentenced in November 2022. A spokesperson said &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/midwest/missouri&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the governor&lt;/a&gt; weighed several factors when making the decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports/chiefs-superfan-xaviar-babudar-pleads-guilty-charges-stemming-bank-robberies&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CHIEFS SUPERFAN XAVIAR BABUDAR PLEADS GUILTY TO CHARGES STEMMING FROM BANK ROBBERIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Reid has completed his alcohol abuse treatment program and has served more prison time than most individuals convicted of similar offenses,&quot; Parson’s office said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reid will also now be required to work at least 30 hours a week and complete 10 hours a month of community service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chiefs communications staff did not immediately respond to an email requesting comment about the commutation from the team or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/sports/nflpa-survey-biggest-takeaways-chiefs-big-red-wins-big-bengals-give-cincinnati-dining-0-star-rating&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Andy Reid&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors said Reid was intoxicated and driving about 84 mph (135 kph) in a 65 mph zone when his Dodge truck hit the cars on an entrance ramp to Interstate 435 near Arrowhead Stadium Feb. 4, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A girl inside one of the cars, Ariel Young, suffered a traumatic brain injury. A total of six people, including Reid, were injured. One of the vehicles he hit had stalled because of a dead battery, and the second was owned by Ariel’s mother, who had arrived to help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reid had a blood alcohol level of 0.113% two hours after the crash, police said. The legal limit is 0.08%. The Chiefs reached a confidential agreement with Ariel’s family to pay for her ongoing medical treatment and other expenses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Associated Press contributed to this report.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Follow Fox News Digital’s &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FoxNewsSports_&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;sports coverage on X&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;, and subscribe to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;the Fox News Sports Huddle newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2022/09/931/523/BrittReid.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">5cfced8b-42cd-555a-84d1-41b9ccaf6c89</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports/nfl/kansas-city-chiefs</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports/nfl</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/sports</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/entertainment/events/in-court</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/sports</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:35:12 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/one-tree-hill-star-bethany-joy-lenz-names-sinister-cult-she-allegedly-spent-decade-in</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/one-tree-hill-star-bethany-joy-lenz-names-sinister-cult-she-allegedly-spent-decade-in</guid>
                    <title>&apos;One Tree Hill&apos; star Bethany Joy Lenz names &apos;sinister&apos; cult she allegedly spent a decade in</title>
                    
                    <description>Bethany Joy Lenz announced her new memoir, &amp;quot;Dinner for Vampires,&amp;quot; which focuses on the actress&amp;apos;s life, including her experience as part of a cult for 10 years.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/one-tree-hill-star-bethany-joy-lenz-suffered-alleged-spiritual-abuse-during-years-cult&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bethany Joy Lenz&lt;/a&gt; is sharing more details about the years she spent in a cult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The actress announced on Instagram that her memoir, &quot;Dinner for Vampires,&quot; will include memories from her time &quot;spent in an abusive, high-demand group (aka, cult).&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Being a writer has been a great, private joy in my life since I was about 12,&quot; she wrote in her Instagram caption. &quot;This isn’t the first book I thought I’d write, publicly, but as difficult as this subject matter is to untangle, I’m grateful I get to share my story, my way.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;It’s a story of forgiveness and a roadmap to how manipulation works, with heartache and humor along the way,&quot; she continued. &quot;We all make mistakes and I hope Dinner for Vampires reminds you that, no matter what weird roads you’ve gone down, you’re not alone.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/bethany-joy-lenz-one-tree-hill-says-she-spent-10-years-cult&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;BETHANY JOY LENZ OF &apos;ONE TREE HILL&apos; SAYS SHE SPENT 10 YEARS IN A CULT: &apos;THERE&apos;S A LOT TO TELL&apos;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The description of the book details Lenz&apos;s journey as a young actress who grew up as an only child and &quot;always wanted a place to belong.&quot; As she got older, she would find &quot;the safe haven she’d been searching for in a Bible study group&quot; composed of others in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Lenz initially found happiness in the group, the description explains it &quot;soon morphed into &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/world/religion/cults&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;something more sinister&lt;/a&gt;,&quot; through &quot;a slowly woven web of manipulation, abuse, and fear under the guise of a church covenant&quot; known as The Big House Family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/C38Nh9wO0wC/?hl=en&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;APP USERS CLICK HERE FOR POST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, Lenz found herself losing all sense of &quot;autonomy,&quot; when she moved into &quot;the Family’s Pacific Northwest compound,&quot; which was run by the &quot;domineering&quot; cult leader. The leader not only convinced her &quot;to marry one of his sons,&quot; but also &quot;steadily drained millions of her TV income without her knowledge.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Family ‘minders’ assigned to her on set, &quot;Maoist struggle session&quot;–inspired meetings in the basement of a filthy house, and regular counseling with ‘Leadership’ were just part of the tactics used to keep her loyal,&quot; the description read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lenz starred on the hit WB teen drama &quot;One Tree Hill&quot; for nine seasons, from 2003 to 2012, having been in the cult the whole time. She played Haley James Scott on the show, the best friend of Chad Michael Murray&apos;s character, Lucas Scott, and wife of his half-brother and former nemesis, Nathan Scott.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lenz previously opened up about the support she felt from her &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/one-tree-hill-star-bethany-joy-lenz-co-stars-attempted-rescue-from-cult-really-committed&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;cast members on the show&lt;/a&gt;, telling the &quot;Biscuits &amp;amp; Jam&quot; podcast in November, when she made the decision to leave the cult, she felt &quot;there were many open arms&quot; waiting to comfort her, and that she found that &quot;very helpful.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I feel like a lot of the people there, whether consciously or subconsciously, knew that just their presence and being an encouragement and letting me know that they still loved and cared about me in spite of the fact that I was a little weird, that made a big difference. It made me feel like there was a safety,&quot; she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;LIKE WHAT YOU’RE READING? CLICK HERE FOR MORE ENTERTAINMENT NEWS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview published Thursday on People, Lenz explained the hardest part about writing &quot;Dinner for Vampires&quot; was having to relive the experiences, saying &quot;exploring the memories, and really facing them,&quot; was really &quot;challenging&quot; for her, but she persevered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since leaving the group, Lenz shared she has gone through &quot;lots of therapy&quot; to overcome what she referred to as &quot;spiritual abuse.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP FOR THE ENTERTAINMENT NEWSLETTER&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Recovery looks different for everyone, depending on your experience of trauma,&quot; she explained. &quot;I had to start from a baseline of my personal understanding of God and the experiences I had had. And then there was a lot of going back to who I was before and remembering that, and then acknowledging that there was so much I just didn’t know.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/entertainment/genres/books&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&quot;Dinner for Vampires&quot;&lt;/a&gt; is set to be published Oct. 22.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/download&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE TO GET THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/bethany.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">1aeb1112-1aef-5baa-af32-c6d27310ea4c</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/entertainment</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/entertainment/tv</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/world/religion/cults</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/entertainment</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:31:59 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/msnbc-host-bashes-georgia-attorney-in-fani-willis-hearing-is-this-the-best-the-das-team-has-to-put-up</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/media/msnbc-host-bashes-georgia-attorney-in-fani-willis-hearing-is-this-the-best-the-das-team-has-to-put-up</guid>
                    <title>MSNBC host bashes Fulton County attorney in Fani Willis hearing: &apos;Is this the best the DA’s team has?&apos;</title>
                    
                    <description>An MSNBC host slammed a Georgia prosecutor in the Fani Willis misconduct hearing, arguing he was difficult to watch in a withering bit of commentary.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/media&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MSNBC host Katy Tur&lt;/a&gt; slammed Georgia prosecutor Adam Abbate on Friday for his performance on behalf of embattled Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis, asking if that was the &quot;best&quot; the county could do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Georgia state judge heard closing arguments Friday on allegations that&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/georgia-judge-set-hear-final-arguments-in-affair-allegations-against-fani-willis&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Willis&apos; romantic relationship&lt;/a&gt; with special prosecutor Nathan Wade benefited her financially and should disqualify her from the election interference case against former President Trump. Abbate said efforts to remove Willis were tantamount to harassment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple news outlets reported on Abbate’s halting speaking style during the course of the hearing. The Atlanta Journal-Constitution was one such news outlet to note the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ajc.com/politics/long-pauses-halting-answers-as-prosecutor-answers-questions-from-judge/JKAYRDPCJJFTZG4TJPICSEZE7E/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;&quot;long pauses and halting answers&lt;/a&gt; as he at times struggled to answer questions from Judge Scott McAfee&quot; and even suggested that Willis at times &quot;seemed eager to step up to the podium and argue the matter herself.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tur spoke to legal expert Melissa Redmon about the ongoing case that has distracted from Trump&apos;s legal woes, noting that Redmon herself had served as the Deputy DA for Fulton County. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fulton-county-da-fani-willis-accused-lying-timing-affair-trump-prosecutor&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;FULTON COUNTY DA FANI WILLIS ACCUSED OF LYING ABOUT TIMING OF AFFAIR WITH TRUMP PROSECUTOR&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I’m struck by… this lawyer is kind of hard to watch,&quot; Tur said. &quot;I mean, as a layman, he’s kind of hard to watch. Is this the best the DA’s team has to put up?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redmon argued that Abbate is a &quot;very good attorney,&quot; saying that from what she can remember, he chiefly handles murder cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &quot;When you talk about these nuanced arguments, I don’t know if this is something he’s used to presenting,&quot; she conceded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redmon then pointed out that there are likely different tactics for different types of trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I would imagine that generally what happens is the whole team gets together, and they flesh out which the strongest points are, which cases should be cited, how the arguments should be presented,&quot; she began.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/text-messages-show-timeline-events-disqualify-fani-willis-trump-camp-asserts&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;TEXT MESSAGES SHOW TIMELINE OF EVENTS TO DISQUALIFY FANI WILLIS, TRUMP CAMP ASSERTS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I think as a trial attorney though, you have to be very disciplined and resist the temptation of going forward with your plan, highlighting the weaknesses of the defense’s argument,&quot; Redmon said. &quot;As opposed to taking the bait from the defense and starting your argument off responding arguing to them, as opposed to enabling yourself to settle in, say what you were going to say and ‘then, by the way, Judge, what they said was wrong, let me tell you why.’&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At one point, Abbate accidentally referred to Willis as &quot;Ms. Wade&quot; before correcting himself, confusing her last name for that of her former romantic partner. &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/Katy-Tur-screencap.png?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/png" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">30cc88c2-0d36-5802-a6ab-9ea4778f20de</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southeast/georgia</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime/trials</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/donald-trump</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/media</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:30:17 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/texas-atm-robber-removes-brinks-security-guards-pants-during-heist-police</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/us/texas-atm-robber-removes-brinks-security-guards-pants-during-heist-police</guid>
                    <title>Texas ATM robber removes Brinks security guard&apos;s pants during heist: police</title>
                    
                    <description>A robbery suspect in Texas made a victim take off his pants during a heist at a Chase Bank ATM on Friday, Irving police said Friday.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/dallas-fort-worth&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dallas-area&lt;/a&gt; Brinks security guard was robbed Friday at gunpoint and forced to take off his pants during the heist, police said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The suspect got out of a black Chevrolet Malibu at 9:45 a.m. and held up a man at a Chase Bank ATM in Irving, the Irving Police Department said in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/world/drug-addict-used-bizarre-object-attempted-post-office-robbery-police&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DRUG ADDICT USED BIZARRE OBJECT IN ATTEMPTED POST OFFICE ROBBERY: POLICE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Video obtained by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fox4news.com/news/brinks-security-guard-pants-atm-irving&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FOX Dallas&lt;/a&gt; shows a man lying on the ground and his pants being taken off by a suspect, so he couldn&apos;t escape or retaliate, police said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The suspect fled with an undisclosed amount of cash, authorities said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Images released by police show the suspect wearing a gray hooded sweater and sweatpants, sunglasses, a cap and a face covering. He was described as Hispanic or White.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://foxnews.com/download&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK TO GET THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators are asking for help in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/crime&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;identifying the suspect&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fox News Digital has reached out to Brinks. &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/03/931/523/Brinks.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">936724a0-23c7-577b-b8e0-db9a3c51511e</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southwest/texas</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/crime/robbery-theft</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/us</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:21:01 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
                <item>
                    <link>https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/adults-only-reality-tv-hit-real-prosecutors-fulton-county</link>
                    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/adults-only-reality-tv-hit-real-prosecutors-fulton-county</guid>
                    <title>It&apos;s an adults-only reality TV hit. Just call it &apos;The Real Prosecutors of Fulton County&apos;</title>
                    
                    <description>Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee&amp;apos;s Atlanta courtroom has been the scene of some unbelievable testimony from prosecutors Fani Willis and Nathan Wade over the past few weeks.</description>

                    
                        <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The fun never sets in the&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/opinion&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Atlanta courtroom&lt;/a&gt; of Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee. That is the red-hot scene of the adults-only reality TV hit called &quot;The Real Prosecutors of Fulton County.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Associated Press observed on Wednesday, a perilous political matter has &quot;taken on a &lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/article/fani-willis-nathan-wade-trump-fulton-county-bradley-07286b56d532c2f52f4336d730fa611d&quot;&gt;soap opera atmosphere&lt;/a&gt;, bogged down by testimony about sex, dating, cash stashes and text messages…&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week’s guest star is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/key-witness-in-fani-wilis-case-testifies-he-may-have-lied-in-texts-about-friends-affair&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Terr​ence Bradley, Esq&lt;/a&gt;., the former law partner of Nathan Wade. Wade, for his part, swims in controversy. He conducted an adulterous relationship with Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis, even while he was married (en route to divorce) and works for Willis as lead prosecutor in her criminal trial related to President Donald J. Trump’s alleged efforts to &quot;overturn&quot; the 2020 election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/georgia-judge-set-hear-final-arguments-in-affair-allegations-against-fani-willis&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TRUMP LAWYERS MAKE CLOSING ARGUMENTS IN DA FANI WILLIS ‘IMPROPER’ AFFAIR ALLEGATIONS: ‘IRREPARABLE STAIN’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bradley testified about when Willis and Wade started their swingin’ affair. He previously had exchanged hundreds of e-mails with Ashleigh Merchant, an attorney for&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/person/donald-trump&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; Trump’s co-defendant Michael Roman&lt;/a&gt;, regarding the timing of Willis and Wade’s romance. In one message, Bradley said that it &quot;absolutely&quot; began before Willis employed Wade in November 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But then Bradley ​contracted courtroom-induced amnesia. Frustrated, Merchant told McAfee: &quot;Judge, he doesn’t remember much of anything right now.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Memories fade. But, alas for Willis and Wade, phone bills are forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wade’s cell phone records are highly incriminating. They show some 2,000 calls and 10,000 text messages between Willis and Wade. They communicated non-stop, with the frenzied back and forth of teenagers in heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/key-witness-in-fani-wilis-case-testifies-he-may-have-lied-in-texts-about-friends-affair&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEY WITNESS IN FANI WILLIS CASE TESTIFIES HE MAY HAVE LIED IN TEXTS ABOUT FRIENDS&apos; AFFAIR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even more revealing are the location data from Wade’s cellphone. They confirm that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nathan-wade-visited-fani-willis-neighborhood-hiring-cellphone-data-indicateshttps://www.foxnews.com/politics/nathan-wade-visited-fani-willis-neighborhood-hiring-cellphone-data-indicates&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wade repeatedly showed up&lt;/a&gt; at Willis’ home ’round midnight and then went home by the dawn’s early light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did they burn the midnight oil reviewing documents and plotting trial procedures or were other things afoot by candlelight?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wade and Willis testified that they &quot;did not sleep together&quot; before Willis hired Wade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the late, great &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-secretary-state-henry-kissinger-dead&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dr. Henry Kissinger&lt;/a&gt; would have put it, this most likely &quot;has the added advantage of being true.&quot; These visits in the wee small hours involved little, if any, actual sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opposing counsel should have asked the obvious question as directly as this: &quot;Did you two have sex before Willis employed Wade?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, Willis paid Wade an enormous sum to argue a complex Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations (RICO) case against a former president of the United States. This is the legal equivalent of starring in the flying trapeze. Wade seems better equipped to drive a clown car. Nonetheless, he got paid like P.T. Barnum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/opinion&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MORE FOX NEWS OPINION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;​Wade has earned some $654,000 from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/politics/georgia-judge-set-hear-final-arguments-in-affair-allegations-against-fani-willis&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Willis’ case against Trump&lt;/a&gt; since January 2022. Fishier still, Willis paid Wade $250 per hour in November and December 2021 while disbursing only $150 per hour to John Floyd, reputedly Georgia’s go-to RICO expert, according to a contract secured by The Daily Caller News Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wade then spent part of this bonanza to take Willis on cruises, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/36-hours-napa-valley-plan-great-weekend&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fabulous weekend in Napa Valley&lt;/a&gt;, and other hot times in posh spots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Willis seems to have recruited Wade in exchange for sexual favors and financial benefits, namely Earth-shaking assignations and splashy vacations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was a giant sexual kickback scheme — call it play to pay — all financed with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/us-regions/southeast/georgia&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fulton County, Georgia’s tax dollars&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Willis hired her boyfriend, then this is corruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Willis hired Wade &lt;i&gt;and then&lt;/i&gt; started copulating with him, then this sounds like sexual harassment: A boss knocking boots with an employee over whom she wields professional and economic power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is either a kickback scam or Me Too in reverse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is it, Fani?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Willis and Wade should be booted from this case. Indeed, this entire stinking wreck should be dismissed and Rudy Giuliani, Mark Meadows, Sidney Powell, Harrison Floyd, Michael Roman, and the other defendants who are being persecuted — or who already have pleaded guilty — should have their charges dropped, their legal fees reimbursed, and profound apologies rendered by people of Fulton County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.foxnews.com/person/m/deroy-murdock&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE FOR MORE FROM DEROY MURDOCK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
                    

                    
                        
                            <media:content url="https://a57.foxnews.com/static.foxnews.com/foxnews.com/content/uploads/2024/01/931/523/Fani-Willis-Nathan-Wade.jpg?ve=1&amp;tl=1" type="image/jpeg" expression="full" width="931" height="523" />
                        
                    
                    
                    

                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.identifier">17dc3fd6-07c0-5b11-acb9-ffafc2a051e2</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/prism.channel">fnc</category>
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/metadata/dc.source">Fox News</category>

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/opinion</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/person/donald-trump</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/us/us-regions/southeast/georgia</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/politics/judiciary</category>
                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/taxonomy">fox-news/politics/elections</category>
                    

                    
                        <category domain="foxnews.com/section-path">fox-news/opinion</category>
                    
                    <category domain="foxnews.com/content-type">article</category>

                    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:18:32 -0500</pubDate>
                </item>
            
        
        
            
            
        
        
            
            
        
        
            
            
        
        
            
            
        
        
            
            
        
        
            
            
        
        

    </channel>
</rss>