<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>TheAHL.com | The American Hockey League</title>
	<atom:link href="https://theahl.com/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://theahl.com</link>
	<description>The official website of the American Hockey League</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:15:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2019/07/cropped-ahl19-32x32.png</url>
	<title>TheAHL.com | The American Hockey League</title>
	<link>https://theahl.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Weekend watch list: Mar. 1-3</title>
		<link>https://theahl.com/weekend-watch-list-mar-1-3?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=weekend-watch-list-mar-1-3</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Patrick Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AHL Notebook]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86579</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Grand Rapids Griffins bring a 16-game points streak (12-0-2-2) into tonight’s date with the Iowa Wild at Van Andel Arena.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-size: 12pt;"><strong><img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-83609" src="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2023/09/story.png" alt="" width="24" height="24" /> <a href="https://theahl.com/author/pwilliams">Patrick Williams</a>, TheAHL.com Features Writer</strong></span></p>
<hr />
<p><a href="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/03/watch24Mar01a.jpg"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-86581 size-medium" src="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/03/watch24Mar01a-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" /></a></p>
<p>The Grand Rapids Griffins are on the move.</p>
<p>They will bring a 16-game points streak (12-0-2-2) into tonight’s date with the Iowa Wild at Van Andel Arena. Their work for the past month and a half has sent them up the Central Division standings into second place.</p>
<p>Helping to lead the way has been Griffins netminder <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9549"><strong>Sebastian Cossa</strong></a>, the latest Howies Hockey Tape/AHL Player of the Week. He has gone 7-0-2 in his past nine decisions, and he recorded his first AHL shutout with 28 stops against Texas on Feb. 21. Then he halted the Milwaukee Admirals’ 19-game winning streak, the second-longest in AHL history, last Sunday with 37 saves in a 4-2 victory. Cossa followed up those efforts with 26 saves on Wednesday as Grand Rapids defeated visiting Iowa, 3-2.</p>
<p>Cossa is a second-year pro who went to the parent Detroit Red Wings 15th overall in the 2021 NHL Draft. In his first full AHL season, he is 13-7-5 with a 2.57 goals-against average and a .912 save percentage in 25 appearances for the Griffins.</p>
<p>A balanced offense has helped the Griffins as well. All-Star forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8912"><strong>Jonatan Berggren</strong></a> has 42 points (17 goals, 25 assists) in 40 games; no other Grand Rapids player has more than 30 points this season, but 10 skaters have recorded at least 20.</p>
<p>The Griffins have not lost in regulation since falling 2-0 to Rockford on Jan. 12.</p>
<hr />
<p><a href="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/03/watch24Mar01b.jpg"><img decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-86582 size-medium" src="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/03/watch24Mar01b-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" /></a></p>
<p>This weekend’s schedule also features a key two-game series in the Atlantic Division with the Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins hosting the Charlotte Checkers tonight and Saturday.</p>
<p>Wilkes-Barre/Scranton opens the weekend third in the Atlantic at 62 points, four points ahead of fifth-place Charlotte. The Penguins have overcome several injuries and recalls to Pittsburgh to move to nine games above .500, matching their highest mark of the season. Wilkes-Barre is without leading scorer <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/6489"><strong>Alex Nylander</strong></a>, who was traded to the Columbus Blue Jackets last Friday.</p>
<p>The Checkers hold a game in hand on Wilkes-Barre/Scranton, however, and have a seven-game point streak (5-0-2-0) after taking a 2-1 win in overtime at Harford on Wednesday. Charlotte has added forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8442"><strong>Jamieson Rees</strong></a> on loan from the Carolina Hurricanes; the second-round pick in the 2019 NHL Draft had just three assists in 31 games with Springfield this season, but he notched 42 points (14 goals, 28 assists) in 65 contests with Chicago in 2022-23.</p>
<p>This weekend’s games will conclude the teams’ season series. They have not met since they split a pair of games in Wilkes-Barre on Dec. 29-30.</p>
<hr />
<p><strong><a href="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/03/watch24Mar01c.jpg"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-86583 size-medium" src="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/03/watch24Mar01c-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" /></a></strong></p>
<p>The San Jose Barracuda welcome the Coachella Valley Firebirds in the <strong>AHLTV Free Game of the Week</strong> on Saturday night (9 ET/6 PT).</p>
<p>First in the Pacific Division at 69 points, the Firebirds are trying to fend off the hard-charging Colorado Eagles. The Firebirds pushed their point streak to four games (3-0-1-0) on Wednesday with a 4-1 win at home against the Barracuda, as <strong><a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/7016">Cameron Hughes</a></strong> scored twice for the Firebirds while <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/5570"><strong>Chris Driedger</strong></a> made 29 saves.</p>
<p>That victory improved Coachella Valley’s all-time record against San Jose to 13-1-0-0, which includes a 7-0-0-0 mark at Tech CU Arena. The Firebirds, who have an eight-game road points streak (5-0-3-0), will first visit Bakersfield tonight as they start a four-game road swing. Nine of their 12 games in March will be away from home.</p>
<p>San Jose forward <strong><a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/6293">Nathan Todd</a></strong> has 13 points (six goals, seven assists) in his past nine games. With 44 points (16 goals, 28 assists) in 52 games overall, he is tied for 11th in league scoring with Coachella Valley captain <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/5611"><strong>Max McCormick</strong></a>.</p>
<p>An AHLTV account is required to watch the AHLTV Free Games of the Week, but no subscription is needed. Visit <a href="http://ahltv.com"><strong>AHLTV.com</strong></a> for details.</p>
<p><span style="font-size: 12pt;"></span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/03/gr-celeb240301-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crookshank, Zellweger, Prosvetov named award winners for February</title>
		<link>https://theahl.com/ahl-award-winners-february-2024?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=ahl-award-winners-february-2024</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AHL PR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 17:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AHL Awards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Belleville Senators]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colorado Eagles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[San Diego Gulls]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86565</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Belleville Senators forward Angus Crookshank, San Diego Gulls defenseman Olen Zellweger and Colorado Eagles goaltender Ivan Prosvetov have been selected as the league’s award winners for February.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>SPRINGFIELD, Mass.</strong> &#8230; The American Hockey League announced today that Belleville Senators forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8648"><strong>Angus Crookshank</strong></a>, San Diego Gulls defenseman <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8873"><strong>Olen Zellweger</strong></a> and Colorado Eagles goaltender <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/7701"><strong>Ivan Prosvetov</strong></a> have been selected as the league’s award winners for February.</p>
<p>Crookshank, the <strong><a href="https://theahl.com/ahl-player-of-the-month-archive">AHL Player of the Month</a></strong>, tallied eight goals and six assists for 14 points in 12 games for Belleville during the month of February.</p>
<p>Crookshank began the month by scoring goals in back-to-back games against Syracuse on Feb. 2 and 3, after which he traveled cross-country to represent the Senators organization at the 2024 AHL All-Star Classic in San Jose, scoring a pair of goals for the North Division during the All-Star Challenge on Feb. 5. Crookshank recorded a goal and two assists in Belleville’s 5-4 win over Utica on Feb. 10, the beginning of a six-game scoring streak. He netted the game-winning goal in a 4-1 decision at Rochester on Feb. 21 and added a goal and an assist in a 4-2 win at Syracuse on Feb. 24 before closing out the month with a goal to help Belleville past Utica, 3-0, on Feb. 28.</p>
<p>Crookshank leads the Senators with 21 goals and 41 points in 45 games this season, his second pro campaign. He made his NHL debut on Dec. 17, 2023, and has recorded one goal and one assist in seven games with Ottawa. The 24-year-old native of North Vancouver, B.C., was a fifth-round pick by Ottawa in the 2018 NHL Draft, and has totaled 52 goals and 52 assists for 104 points in 135 career AHL contests.</p>
<p>Zellweger, the <strong><a href="https://theahl.com/ahl-rookie-of-the-month-archive">AHL Rookie of the Month</a></strong>, posted four goals and eight assists for 12 points in 10 games for San Diego during February.</p>
<p>After participating in the AHL All-Star Classic on Feb. 4 and 5, Zellweger totaled five points in the Gulls’ two-game sweep of a visit to Calgary, recording two assists on Feb. 9 and notching a goal and two assists on Feb. 10. Zellweger scored another goal against San Jose on Feb. 14, then registered two assists and eight shots on goal at Bakersfield on Feb. 20. He scored again on Feb. 24 vs. Ontario, and chipped in a goal and an assist at Texas on Feb. 28.</p>
<p>A second-round choice by Anaheim in the 2021 NHL Draft, Zellweger ranks third among all AHL defensemen and tied for third among all AHL rookies with 37 points in 44 games for the Gulls. The 20-year-old native of Calgary, Alta., also has one assist in four games with the Ducks after making his NHL debut on Jan. 23, 2024.</p>
<p>Prosvetov, the <strong><a href="https://theahl.com/ahl-goaltender-of-the-month-archive">AHL Goaltender of the Month</a></strong>, allowed two goals or fewer in each of his eight starts during February, going 8-0-0 with a 1.25 goals-against average, a .959 save percentage and two shutouts while stopping 231 of 241 shots overall.</p>
<p>Assigned to the Eagles on Feb. 4, Prosvetov made his debut with the club on Feb. 9 and turned aside 26 shots in a 3-1 win over Abbotsford. He made 38 saves in a 3-2 victory over the Canucks on Feb. 10, and was named Howies Hockey Tape/AHL Player of the Week after stopping 93 of 98 shots in defeating Bakersfield twice and Coachella Valley once between Feb. 14 and Feb. 18. Prosvetov then notched back-to-back shutouts against Henderson, making 15 saves on Feb. 23 and 27 stops on Feb. 24, before closing out the month with a 32-save performance at Abbotsford on Feb. 27.</p>
<p>Prosvetov was acquired by the Colorado Avalanche off waivers from Arizona on Oct. 9, 2023, and has made 11 NHL appearances this season, going 4-3-1 with a 3.16 goals-against average and an .895 save percentage. A 24-year-old native of Moscow, Russia, Prosvetov has a record of 62-54-10 with a 3.17 GAA, an .899 save percentage and six shutouts in 133 career AHL games with Colorado and Tucson. The fourth-round pick by Arizona in the 2018 NHL Draft has appeared in 24 games in the NHL between the Avalanche and Coyotes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/monthly240301-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Poirier easing his way back to Wranglers</title>
		<link>https://calgarywranglers.com/get-my-swagger-back/#new_tab?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=poirier-easing-his-way-back-to-wranglers</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AHL PR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 23:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Calgary Wranglers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jeremie Poirier was a welcome sight at Calgary Wranglers practice this week. The 21-year-old defenseman started the season with seven points (1g,6a) in four games, but suffered a forearm laceration on Oct. 21 that has kept him out of the lineup ever since.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jeremie Poirier was a welcome sight at Calgary Wranglers practice this week. The 21-year-old defenseman started the season with seven points (1g,6a) in four games, but suffered a forearm laceration on Oct. 21 that has kept him out of the lineup ever since.</p>
<p><a href="https://calgarywranglers.com/get-my-swagger-back/">https://calgarywranglers.com/get-my-swagger-back/</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/poirier_jeremie240229-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prosvetov making most of time with Eagles</title>
		<link>https://theahl.com/prosvetov-making-most-of-time-with-eagles?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=prosvetov-making-most-of-time-with-eagles</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Patrick Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colorado Eagles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86548</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ivan Prosvetov understands the Colorado Avalanche’s plan, and he has been making the most of his time with the AHL Eagles.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-size: 12pt;"><strong><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-83609" src="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2023/09/story.png" alt="" width="24" height="24" /> <a href="https://theahl.com/author/pwilliams">Patrick Williams</a>, TheAHL.com Features Writer</strong></span></p>
<hr />
<p><a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/7701"><strong>Ivan Prosvetov</strong></a>’s big break came last October.</p>
<p>After four seasons in the Arizona Coyotes organization – mostly spent in the AHL with the Tucson Roadrunners – Prosvetov headed off to the Colorado Avalanche after they claimed him off waivers on Oct. 9. And for a while that break held for the 24-year-old Prosvetov, who had been a 2018 fourth-round pick by the Arizona. Working behind <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/6844"><strong>Alexandar Georgiev</strong></a>, Prosvetov had a job with a Stanley Cup contender and spent the first four months of this season in the NHL.</p>
<p>Prosvetov has been down this path before. He showed steady progress with the Arizona organization, becoming a number-one with Tucson and challenging for NHL work. Across three seasons with the Coyotes, he ended up playing 13 games in a recall role. But <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/6720"><strong>Connor Ingram</strong></a>’s 2022 arrival in the organization – via waivers from Nashville nearly a year to the day before Prosvetov’s departure – meant that Prosvetov would have to find a different path to the NHL.</p>
<p>So it goes sometimes when you’re an AHL prospect trying to break through full-time to an NHL job. Ingram, along with so many other prospects, had taken that route. So would Prosvetov, and the opportunity with Colorado was a good one.</p>
<p>“You know what?” he said. “It’s always a new opportunity, a new challenge to start with a new team. It was the first time in my career. It was really exciting.”</p>
<p>It still is, even if Prosvetov again finds himself back in the AHL. Playing time had been hard to find, who appeared in only 11 games with the Avs. Meanwhile, fellow prospect <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8731"><strong>Justus Annunen</strong></a> had shown well with the Colorado Eagles. So after clearing waivers, Prosvetov joined the Eagles nearly a month after his last game action.</p>
<p>Prosvetov understands the Avalanche’s plan, and he has gotten plenty of time in net since then with the Eagles. He debuted at home on Feb. 9 with a 26-save performance against Abbotsford in a 3-1 win. A night later, he had 38 saves in another victory against the Canucks. Another 38-save effort came Feb. 17 at Coachella Valley. And there are the back-to-back shutouts this past weekend at home against Henderson. For his latest display, Prosvetov moved his record to 8-0-0 after he led the Eagles to a 5-2 victory at Abbotsford last night, making 32 stops.</p>
<p>Colorado has now won 16 of its last 19 games, and tonight’s rematch with the Canucks gives them a chance to pull even with Coachella Valley for the Pacific Division lead.</p>
<p>A very rangy 6-foot-5 and 189 pounds, Prosvetov did not come to the Colorado organization needing to have his game rebuilt.</p>
<p>“I’m really a system goalie,” said Prosvetov, who worked with Avalanche goaltending coach <strong>Jussi Parkkila </strong>in the NHL. “The net-play system, the traffic, the stance management, all that kind of stuff. The goalie coach is like your navigation [system]. If you sometimes go the wrong way, he can bring you back to your fundamentals, and I think that Jussi is really good at it.”</p>
<p>With the Eagles, Prosvetov works with Avs goalie development coach <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/5211"><strong>Peter Budaj</strong></a>, someone who had to battle to make the NHL himself just like Prosvetov is now. Budaj spent three seasons in the AHL with the Hershey Bears before breaking through with the Avalanche in 2005. Then, on the back end of his career, he was named the AHL’s outstanding goaltender in 2015-16 with the Ontario Reign and earned a return to the NHL, extending his career by three more seasons with Los Angeles and Tampa Bay.</p>
<p>“He’s a great coach,” Prosvetov said of his new mentor, “and he was a great goalie. That’s a guy you can trust.”</p>
<p>The Eagles won’t be back home until a two-game series with Calgary in mid-March, but Prosvetov and the team’s fans have already established a quick bond. Familiar with Eagles fans from his days visiting with Tucson, Prosvetov is now the beneficiary of their very vocal, very spirited support inside Blue Arena.</p>
<p>“The fans are awesome,” Prosvetov said. “It was tough (as a visitor), but at the same time it was fun because sometimes that gets me going when everyone is against you. It was a fun time to play against them, and now to have all those fans on your side&#8230; when they cheer you on after every save, it really helps you. It helps you mentally. It gives you more energy.</p>
<p>“It’s good to be on the good side.”</p>
<p><span style="font-size: 12pt;"></span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/prosvetov_ivan240228-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hard work keeps paying off for Rifai</title>
		<link>https://thehockeynews.com/nhl/toronto-maple-leafs/latest-news/when-nobodys-watching-hes-still-working-how-marshall-rifai-turned-an-ahl-contract-into-a-nhl-debut-with-the-maple-leafs#new_tab?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=hard-work-keeps-paying-off-for-rifai</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AHL PR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 15:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toronto Marlies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86550</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hard work and determination can get anyone anywhere. Marshall Rifai, who made his NHL debut with Toronto last week, is the latest example of that.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hard work and determination can get anyone anywhere. Marshall Rifai, who made his NHL debut with Toronto last week, is the latest example of that.</p>
<p><a href="https://thehockeynews.com/nhl/toronto-maple-leafs/latest-news/when-nobodys-watching-hes-still-working-how-marshall-rifai-turned-an-ahl-contract-into-a-nhl-debut-with-the-maple-leafs">https://thehockeynews.com/nhl/toronto-maple-leafs/latest-news/when-nobodys-watching-hes-still-working-how-marshall-rifai-turned-an-ahl-contract-into-a-nhl-debut-with-the-maple-leafs</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/rifai_marshall240228-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mitchell staying close to the game in retirement</title>
		<link>https://theahl.com/mitchell-staying-close-to-the-game-in-retirement?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=mitchell-staying-close-to-the-game-in-retirement</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AHL PR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 19:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[AHL On The Beat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hershey Bears]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86541</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[FOX43 sports director Todd Sadowski talked with former Hershey Bears captain Garrett Mitchell about his retirement from hockey and the transition away from the game he’s been playing since he was a kid.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-83609" src="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2023/09/story.png" alt="" width="24" height="24" /> <a href="https://theahl.com/tag/ahl-on-the-beat">AHL On The Beat</a></strong></p>
<hr />
<p style="font-weight: 400;">FOX43 sports director <strong>Todd Sadowski</strong> talked with former Hershey Bears captain <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/3547"><strong>Garrett Mitchell</strong></a> about his retirement from hockey and the transition away from the game he’s been playing since he was a kid.</p>
<p style="font-weight: 400;">They discuss why Garrett was named a captain on his team so often and the characteristics that made him a leader on and off the ice. They also talk about his first year as a TV analyst for Bears games, the difference between playing the game ice at ice level and describing it from up in the booth, and what makes the Bears an elite organization in the American Hockey League.</p>
<div class="video-container embed-container"><iframe loading="lazy" title="Former Hershey Bear Garrett Mitchell talks retirement, transition to TV" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FMvmYSyg1jI?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/mitchell_garrett240227-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joshua’s physical style translating well in rookie season</title>
		<link>https://www.post-gazette.com/sports/penguins/2024/02/27/penguins-pipeline-jagger-joshua-physicality-full-ahl-season-joel-blomqvist/stories/202402260040#new_tab?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=joshuas-physical-style-translating-well-in-rookie-season</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AHL PR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86535</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jagger Joshua’s first full AHL season has come with all sorts of takeaways. He has learned that his game can indeed translate from the college ranks to the pros, yet he has as much to learn away from the ice as he still does on it.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jagger Joshua’s first full AHL season has come with all sorts of takeaways. He has learned that his game can indeed translate from the college ranks to the pros, yet he has as much to learn away from the ice as he still does on it.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.post-gazette.com/sports/penguins/2024/02/27/penguins-pipeline-jagger-joshua-physicality-full-ahl-season-joel-blomqvist/stories/202402260040">https://www.post-gazette.com/sports/penguins/2024/02/27/penguins-pipeline-jagger-joshua-physicality-full-ahl-season-joel-blomqvist/stories/202402260040</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/joshua_jagger240227-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stankoven celebrates birthday with first NHL points</title>
		<link>https://www.nhl.com/stars/news/heika-s-take-logan-stankoven-excels-as-dallas-stars-come-up-just-short-against-new-york-islanders#new_tab?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=stankoven-celebrates-birthday-with-first-nhl-points</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AHL PR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 14:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Texas Stars]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86533</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[AHL scoring leader Logan Stankoven had a goal and an assist for the Dallas Stars on his 21st birthday Monday night, and sure looked like a guy who can play in the NHL.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="d3-l-grid--outer ">
<div class="nhl-c-article__body d3-l-grid--inner">
<div class="d3-l-col__col-12 ">
<div class="oc-c-body-part oc-c-markdown-stories">
<p>AHL scoring leader <a href="https://www.nhl.com/player/8482702">Logan Stankoven</a> had a goal and an assist for the Dallas Stars on his 21st birthday Monday night, and sure looked like a guy who can play in the NHL.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p><a href="https://www.nhl.com/stars/news/heika-s-take-logan-stankoven-excels-as-dallas-stars-come-up-just-short-against-new-york-islanders">https://www.nhl.com/stars/news/heika-s-take-logan-stankoven-excels-as-dallas-stars-come-up-just-short-against-new-york-islanders</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/stankoven_logan240227-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Recalls, injuries not slowing down Bears</title>
		<link>https://theahl.com/recalls-injuries-not-slowing-down-bears?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=recalls-injuries-not-slowing-down-bears</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Patrick Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 21:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Features]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hershey Bears]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86527</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fortunes swing quickly in the American Hockey League. And despite the recent bumps in the road, the Hershey Bears are still on pace for a record-breaking season.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-size: 12pt;"><strong><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-83609" src="https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2023/09/story.png" alt="" width="24" height="24" /> <a href="https://theahl.com/author/pwilliams">Patrick Williams</a>, TheAHL.com Features Writer</strong></span></p>
<hr />
<p>Fortunes swing quickly in the American Hockey League.</p>
<p>Earlier today, rookie forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9972"><strong>Ivan Miroshnichenko</strong></a> was recalled from Hershey by the Washington Capitals. The 20-year-old Miroshnichenko, a 2022 first-round pick, is having a solid season with the Bears with 25 points (nine goals, 16 assists) through 47 games.</p>
<p>On Friday, hours before a game against Wilkes-Barre/Scranton, Hershey lost forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9354"><strong>Hendrix Lapierre</strong></a> to recall. Before that it was <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9515"><strong>Pierrick Dube</strong></a>, who took his 24 goals (tied for fourth-most in the AHL) with him to Washington to make his NHL debut. Bears leading scorer <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/4589"><strong>Mike Sgarbossa</strong></a> left for Washington during the All-Star break and is taking a regular shift with the Capitals, showing no sign of returning to Hershey.</p>
<p>On Feb. 15, the Capitals put forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/6729"><strong>Matthew Phillips</strong></a> on waivers. A 30-goal scorer in the AHL each of the last two seasons, Phillips would have been a massive addition if he was assigned to Hershey. Instead the rival Pittsburgh Penguins claimed him, keeping him in the NHL.</p>
<p>And then there is AHL All-Star <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9112"><strong>Ethen Frank</strong></a>, who has been injured and out since Feb. 9. Versatile center <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/7648"><strong>Riley Sutter</strong></a> has missed the last four games. Captain <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/4119"><strong>Dylan McIlrath</strong></a> served a two-game league suspension.</p>
<p>These Bears are hobbling. But so it goes in the AHL. And so it goes that a made-in-Hershey theme is nothing new for the Capitals, where Bears alumni have made major impacts in the nation’s capital since their affiliation began in 2005.</p>
<p>And despite the recent bumps in the road, Hershey is 5-1-0-1 since the All-Star break and has just five regulation losses in its last 42 outings (32-5-0-3). For the 12-time Calder Cup champions, this regular season may be shaping up as their finest yet: playing at an .802 clip with 19 games remaining, they are on pace to surpass the 1992-93 Binghamton Rangers’ standard (.775) for the best record in league history.</p>
<p>The Bears certainly aren’t cruising, especially now. They had to grind out five of six points on a swing through Toronto, Belleville and Laval last week. Then came a nine-hour bus ride home before back-to-back games hosting Wilkes-Barre/Scranton and Rochester. Before a packed house at Giant Center on Friday, <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8015"><strong>Chase Priskie</strong></a> scored the go-ahead goal with 3:38 left in regulation to send the Bears to a 4-1 win over the Penguins. And in front of another sell-out crowd on Saturday, they ripped 39 shots at Rochester’s <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/10002"><strong>Devon Levi</strong></a> – 22 of them in the second period – before <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8657"><strong>Alex Limoges</strong></a> gave Hershey a 2-1 win with his third overtime marker this season.</p>
<p>“It was a total team effort,” head coach <strong>Todd Nelson</strong> said after Friday’s win. “All in all, it was a great effort from everybody. Like I always say, they all can’t be Picassos.”</p>
<p>Nelson has won the Calder Cup four times, including last year’s championship with the Bears. He consistently preaches that the regular season is a time to learn hard lessons, which is why he rarely raises too many alarms if his club has a bad night or two. Those stumbles, Nelson reasons, are part of that process. (Of course, he is also not one to make much of a run of success, either.) There is no time in the postseason to learn those lessons, especially when a slip or two in a short series can bring an abrupt and early end to any Calder Cup hopes.</p>
<p>For much of the season, the Bears had remained rather healthy and the calls from Washington were minimal. With a deep roster, finding playing time for everybody was difficult. That is no longer a problem, and players who had sought more then now have all the ice time that they can handle, including opportunities on the power play. <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/8809"><strong>Tyson Empey</strong></a> and <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9589"><strong>Kevin O’Neil</strong></a> were the latest additions from the Bears’ ECHL affiliate in South Carolina.</p>
<p>“It’s put up or shut up,” Nelson said bluntly. “Go out there, do your job, and show that you can play there. The guys have done a pretty good job of that.”</p>
<p>That Toronto-Belleville-Laval swing helped as well.</p>
<p>“I think it was a huge stepping stone for us in terms of guys stepping up,” said Priskie, whose 29 points (six goals, 23 assists) in 51 games lead all Hershey blueliners. “You look down the list, and it seems like we have a depleted core. However, guys are stepping into new roles, and they’re thriving. You look at a guy like <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/7584"><strong>Matt Strome</strong></a>, he had to bide his time waiting to get his chance full-time on the fourth line. Then in an elevated role, he goes out and has a goal and an assist (against the Penguins), which is just huge for our club.</p>
<p>Nelson had Strome and <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9161"><strong>Bogdan Trineyev</strong></a> killing a penalty in the final minutes of regulation on Friday while holding a one-goal lead. Both picked up empty-net shorthanded goals on that kill. Rookie forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/9818"><strong>Ryan Hofer</strong></a> had a goal the same night. At some point the Bears may get some of their top point-getters back with fresh NHL know-how. But for now they have a new contingent of personnel who have shown that they can compete and win games in the AHL.</p>
<p>“Guys [are] being thrust into new roles,” Priskie said, “and having to elevate their game to make sure we continue to sustain success.”</p>
<p><span style="font-size: 12pt;"></span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2024/02/her-celeb240226-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thunderbirds’ Vrana suspended for two games</title>
		<link>https://theahl.com/vrana-suspended-24feb26?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=vrana-suspended-24feb26</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AHL PR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 21:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Springfield Thunderbirds]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://theahl.com/?p=86530</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Springfield Thunderbirds forward Jakub Vrana has been suspended for two games as a consequence of his actions during a game at Bridgeport on Feb. 25.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>SPRINGFIELD, Mass.</strong> … The American Hockey League’s Player Safety Committee today announced that Springfield Thunderbirds forward <a href="https://theahl.com/stats/player/5943"><strong>Jakub Vrana</strong></a> has been suspended for two (2) games as a consequence of his actions during a game at Bridgeport on Feb. 25.</p>
<p>Vrana was assessed a game misconduct under the provisions of AHL Rule 75.5(ii) for using an obscene gesture.</p>
<p>Vrana will miss Springfield’s games Friday (Mar. 1) at Providence and Saturday (Mar. 2) vs. Laval.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<image><url>https://theahl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2023/10/ahl1200e-1024x576.jpg</url></image>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
